All right,
Speaker 1: guys. Welcome in. Welcome in. I think I have something else still playing in the background. I got to kill that. There we go. Guys, welcome in. We're going to have a big show tonight. I hope you have your pen and paper handy. I hope you have your screen capper
handy
Speaker 2: or your cell phone or somehow you can take pictures of stuff because we have a lot to cover. If you saw last night's program, we're going to do a little recap before we get going because there were some questions about the airplane timeline and I want to put my
my
Speaker 2: suppositions.
Speaker 3: I want to add my suppositions into there. So we'll get that done. Uh, and then we will jump into the audio. The
Speaker 1: opening, I think is going to be fantastic. I've been looking for a place to sneak this opening in and I had to rework it a little bit to make it match tonight's
Speaker 2: topic, but it's great. It's fantastic. I've been looking forward to this for a long time. Um, so I'm, I'm really excited. Yes. Those of you who went with
Speaker 2: rare
Speaker 4: prime rib hoodie you got it right bean paste hoodie uh raw hamburger meat
Speaker 5: hoodie refried bean hoodie whatever else you have here uh this is your color of the day your fbi color of the day redacted
so we'll got we'll get
Speaker 6: you guys squared away if you uh if you have any questions feel free join in the chat we'll go over those towards the end of the program um
Let me do this
Speaker 7: real quickly because I have to stall for about three minutes
Speaker 5: in order to not have the algo go crazy when I start doing my opening because it's a violent opening. So I want to go over this real quickly from yesterday.
Speaker 8: Just to recap, you can screen
Speaker 9: cap this at any time. You can take a picture of it. This is my opening.
Speaker 9: guess my opinion on when people arrived.
Speaker 2: We've added names. We've added names. So this Tango Whiskey flight, for example, at 9 a.m., that's Erica in my new timeline. I'm not married to this timeline.
Speaker 10: I'm open to being wrong.
But we'll play
Speaker 10: some audio
Speaker 1: tonight that might suggest I'm right.
That might
Speaker 1: suggest I'm right. And that would make the flight that came in, we thought was Erica at 3.12 p.m.,
That
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): would put Andrew on that flight, and then we will explain that. So we're going to pull this back up in a little bit. We're
going to pull this
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): back up in a little bit, but I am going to refer to this a few times tonight. So just stay tuned, be
ready,
Speaker 8: have your pen and paper handy, because if
Speaker 12: you were confused on the timeline, the audio tonight may get you, but the audio is critical because we haven't listened to this in a long time, and we know a ton more about the Charlie Kirk case today than we did then.
and
Speaker 2: so we will uh we've got to get this all cleared up cleared up we have to get on the same page we have to do a little review uh i've got some delicious
Speaker 13: blackberry soda tonight and the thing i'm not drinking booze this delicious blackberry soda um and i'm already
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): halfway done with it i hope that doesn't lead to me having to use the restroom and wiggle around for the last half hour of the
program again it's
Speaker 15: been known to happen
Speaker 16: all
right let
Speaker 16: me give you um Let
me give
Speaker 16: you the open.
Speaker 16: The open is a banger in
my opinion, in my
Speaker 17: opinion, I'm not going to tell, I'm not going to tell you what you have to believe about it. I'm just telling you right now, when I look at this opening, it's
a
Speaker 2: banger. It's
Speaker 18: a, it's a subject that just drives people crazy when you,
when
Speaker 3: you cover it. So, all right. I don't know where the goblet came from. I saw somebody in the chat asking,
Speaker 19: I don't know. I don't know.
Speaker 19: Oh, and just to clear up something else, I picked the color of the
Speaker 1: hoodie an hour or two before the program. I'm not watching you guys guess and then picking one
that you
Speaker 1: guys don't guess. I wouldn't do
that to you. I wouldn't do that
Speaker 1: to you. All right, ladies and gentlemen, you ready?
Here is
Speaker 10: your opening statement. Orenthal James Simpson, O.J. Simpson, was at one time one of the most famous I'll see you next time.
Speaker 10: and beloved people in America. O.J. was born in 1947 in San Francisco. He was raised in
Speaker 20: extremely humble circumstances, plagued by poverty and health
challenges. As a
Speaker 10: child, he had rickets caused by severe nutrient deficiencies and required leg braces. He overcame his
Speaker 10: Early physical challenges and found his
Speaker 20: first taste of stardom as the star football player at the University of Southern California, where he became a college football legend.
In 1968,
Speaker 20: Simpson won the Heisman Trophy as the nation's top football player, rushing for over 1,700 yards
and scoring
Speaker 20: 22 touchdowns in a single season. His speed, power, and elusiveness on the field
Speaker 20: Combined with his catchy initials, O.J. earned him the nickname The Juice, a moniker that
Speaker 21: would follow him throughout his life. After college, O.J. was selected by the Buffalo Bills as the first overall draft pick in the 1969 NFL Draft. His legendary
Speaker 12: professional career solidified his status as one of American football's all-time greats. In 1973, O.J. solidified his status and became the first
Speaker 20: player ever.
To rush
Speaker 20: for over 2,000 yards in a single season, he led the league in rushing four times, earned six Pro Bowl selections, and was named NFL MVP in 1973. His on-field dominance, his electric personality, and his stunning good looks gave him tremendous crossover
appeal and made him a
Speaker 20: household
Speaker 21: name. His infectious smile graced magazine covers and television screens. By the mid-1970s, he was not
Speaker 20: just an athlete, but a cultural icon.
Speaker 20: Becoming one of the driving personalities able to bridge racial divides in a post-civil rights era America.
After hanging up his
Speaker 20: cleats from football in 1979, Simpson parlayed his fame into a successful entertainment career.
Being larger than
Speaker 20: life, he smoothly and seamlessly transitioned to Hollywood. He starred in films like The Towering Inferno and The Naked Gun Trilogy, whereas comedic timing as Detective Nordberg
Speaker 20: showcased his
Speaker 12: lighter side
his role
Speaker 12: in hertz rental car commercials famously sprinting through airports became iconic embedding him as a true pop culture icon simpson also worked as a sports broadcaster for abc and nbc offering insightful commentary that kept him squarely in the public eye endorsements rolled in from schick razors to
Speaker 20: pioneer chicken and he amassed a fortune of tens of millions of dollars.
His
Speaker 20: personal life amplified his celebrity. He married Marguerite Whitley in 1967. He had three children. He later divorced Marguerite and married Nicole Brown in 1985. The
couple blended
Speaker 20: into Beverly Hills elite circles. He hobnobbed with celebrities, politicians, and business moguls. O.J. Simpson embodied the American dream. Polls
in the
Speaker 20: early 1990s?
Speaker 20: showed him as one of the most admired men in America with approval ratings rivaling Michael Jordan's.
His fame
Speaker 20: was massive. Sports Illustrated
Speaker 22: called him the most famous athlete in America. Simpson represented success, charm, and crossover appeal, a symbol
Speaker 20: of black achievement in a white-dominated society. Before June, 1994, he was untouchable.
It's hard
Speaker 20: to quantify for people who were not around at the time and only remember that,
the
Speaker 20: controversial O.J. Simpson, just how big he was. He was a larger-than-life personality whose legacy seemed destined for immortality.
On the night of June
Speaker 20: 12, 1994, Nicole Brown Simpson and her friend Ron Goldman were brutally murdered outside of Nicole's Britwood, California condominium on Bundy Drive. The prosecution, led by Marsha Clark and Christopher Darden, argued that O.J. Simpson
Speaker 20: driven by possessive obsession over his ex-wife, committed the double homicide in a fit of domestic fury. Their case hinged on a timeline of escalating abuse, physical evidence collected at the
scene and at Simpson's
Speaker 20: house and his suspicious behavior after the murder.
The story
Speaker 22: began with Simpson's history of domestic violence against Nicole. Police records showed multiple incidents.
These
Speaker 22: include a
Speaker 20: 1989 plea of no contest to spousal battery. Prosecutors introduced 911 tapes from a 1993 call where Nicole pleaded for help as O.J. Simpson kicked down her door. This pattern, they claim, culminated in murder after Nicole ended their attempts to reconcile their marriage. On June 12th, Nicole attended her daughter Sydney's dance recital. O.J. Simpson also was at
Speaker 12: the recital, but
the two
Speaker 12: reportedly ignored
each other.
Speaker 12: Prosecutors argued this snub ignited his jealousy.
The murders occurred
Speaker 21: around 10.15 p.m., according to a witness.
The neighbor heard a
Speaker 21: dog barking
Speaker 20: incessantly from 10.15 to 10.35, and another saw a shadowy figure fleeing the scene.
Nicole was
Speaker 20: found with severe knife wounds to her throat and multiple stab wounds to her body in what appeared to be a frenzied attack.
A
Speaker 20: local waiter named Ron Goldman had arrived at Nicole's house to return a pair of glasses that she had left at his restaurant. He suffered defensive wounds that indicated a serious and sustained struggle. He ultimately succumbed to fatal stab wounds to his neck and chest. The prosecution produced a timeline that placed Simpson at the scene. He had no alibi between
the time
Speaker 20: after he dropped his daughter off at 9.40 p.m. until 10.54 p.m.,
Speaker 20: when a limo driver arrived to take him to the airport for a red-eye flight to Chicago.
Key evidence tied
Speaker 20: Simpson directly to the crimes. Blood drops at the scene matched his DNA. Odds
of a
Speaker 20: random match were put at 1 in 170 million. A bloody glove found at Bundy matched one discovered behind Simpson's Rockingham estate. Each glove contained DNA from OJ, Nicole, and Ron Goldman.
A
Speaker 20: pair of size 12 Bruno Mali shoes left bloody footprints at the scene. Prosecutors later produced photos of Simpson wearing size 12 Bruno Mali shoes. Simpson's Ford Bronco had blood stains smeared inside and cuts on his left
hand
Speaker 22: the next day were unexplained. Prosecutors positioned Simpson's post-murder actions as quite incriminating.
He
Speaker 22: boarded his flight
Speaker 20: calmly, but left a bloody trail, a bloody sock in his bedroom contained Nicole's DNA. A
knit cap at the scene
Speaker 22: had hairs consistent with Simpson's. The infamous and nationally televised slow speed Bronco chase on June 17, where Simpson held a gun to his head in the back seat while his friend Al Cowlings drove, was portrayed by the prosecution as a confession of guilt.
Speaker 22: Inside the Bronco, the police found a disguise kit. They found a passport and $8,000 in cash. They argued this was evidence Simpson was intending to flee. The prosecution argued he had motive, opportunity, and means. The motive was jealousy. The opportunity was a time window without an alibi. And the means were Simpson's physical strength as a former all-world athlete. The prosecution dismissed what they characterized as conspiracy theories,
and
Speaker 22: emphasized instead the evidence of his guilt being overwhelming.
In closing, Prosecutor
Speaker 21: Marsha Clark urged the jury to see Simpson not as a celebrity, but as a domestic batterer turned killer.
She said the
Speaker 21: murders were the final ultimate
act of control. The
Speaker 20: narrative
Speaker 10: framed Simpson as a fallen idol whose charm masked a monster, with the evidence forming an unbreakable chain. The defense said,
The
Speaker 22: defense was led by attorneys who were dubbed the dream team. The
dream team
Speaker 22: included people like Johnny Cochran, Bob Shapiro,
Speaker 20: and F. Lee Bailey, among others. The defense aggressively challenged each piece of the prosecution's evidence, but they particularly keyed in on the prosecution's timeline. They argued it made Simpson's involvement highly unlikely, if not impossible.
Their
Speaker 20: strategy centered on compressing the window of opportunity to an absurdly tight frame, highlighting inconsistencies, police errors, and alternative explanations to sow reasonable doubt. The
Speaker 21: prosecution's witnesses pegged the murders very close to 10.15 p.m. The defense seized on this time and argued Simpson simply did not have time to commit the acts, get cleaned up, dispose of the evidence, and then appear mostly normal shortly thereafter.
Key to
Speaker 21: their argument was Simpson's whereabouts. At 9.37 p.m., he called his
Speaker 20: girlfriend, Paula Barbieri, from his Bronco, sounding completely normal.
By 10.03
Speaker 20: p.m., Cato Kalin, who lived in Simpson's guest house, heard him return home
Speaker 21: after dropping off his daughter at the recital. Kalin testified to thumps on his guest house wall around 10.40 or 10.45 p.m.,
which
Speaker 21: the defense suggested were from an intruder or evidence planter and not O.J. Simpson disposing of items. The
limo driver
Speaker 21: arrived at 10.22 to take O.J. Simpson to the airport, testified he did not see the Bronco until 10.55 when Simpson went to the limo claiming he'd overslept
and cut his hand
Speaker 21: rushing to pack. The
driver noted
Speaker 22: Simpson seemed composed, loading bags without any signs of recent violence.
This is where
Speaker 22: the timeline comes in to be critical to the O.J. Simpson case. The defense calculated the timeline
Speaker 12: meticulously. From Nicole's condo to Simpson's estate was a 10-15 minute drive, even in the lightest traffic. Forensic experts testified that it would take at least 10-15
Speaker 20: minutes to commit the brutal murders,
complete with a
Speaker 21: defensive struggle from one of the victims. After
that, he
Speaker 21: would have needed time to clean up the blood.
to
Speaker 21: change his clothes, to dispose of the weapon that was never found.
Experts estimated this would
Speaker 21: add another 10 to 15 minutes minimum.
This left just
Speaker 21: 35 minutes to drive back home, hide all the evidence, take a shower, pack for Chicago, and
meet the
Speaker 21: limo driver when he first saw him at 10.54 p.m. Defense attorney Barry Sheck emphasized this was physically impossible for one person to do without leaving an obvious trace of guilt.
This was
Speaker 21: especially true, he argued,
Speaker 20: since Simpson had no visible blood or any injuries beyond a small cut seen by the limo driver.
The defense
Speaker 20: also attacked the blood evidence found at the scene, EDTA, EDTA, this is a preservative in blood vials. EDTA was detected on
Speaker 12: both the sock and the gate.
at
Speaker 12: O.J.'s house. The defense argued that the presence of EDTA necessarily meant the
Speaker 20: evidence was planted after Simpson's blood was taken.
There was
Speaker 20: also the famous
Speaker 21: glove demonstration where Simpson struggled to fit the glove on his hand in open court. Johnny Cochran used this incident
Speaker 20: to coin what is perhaps the most famous line ever uttered in a courtroom. If it doesn't fit, you must acquit. The
defense introduced
Speaker 20: alternative timelines via experts.
Dr.
Speaker 20: Michael Baden argued the victim's body temperature and rigor mortis suggested a later time of death, perhaps closer to 11 p.m., after Simpson was already en route to the airport. Phone records showed a call from Simpson's cell phone at 10.03 p.m., and it was near his home, not near Nicole's home at Bundy. They highlighted rushed police work. The scene wasn't secured until 12.30 a.m., allowing crime scene contamination.
By
Speaker 20: poking holes in the unaccounted for minutes, the flawed forensics, and the biased investigation, the defense argued Simpson's guilt was not just doubtful, but
it was in
Speaker 20: fact a logistical impossibility. Their strategy resonated. It led to an acquittal after less than four hours of
jury
Speaker 23: deliberation. So
if O.J.
Speaker 23: Simpson didn't do it, who did?
Speaker 20: Investigator William Deere
Speaker 20: wrote a 2012 book called O.J. is Innocent and I Can Prove It.
In it, he
Speaker 21: argued the real perpetrator was a young man named Jason Simpson. Jason was O.J.'s son from his first marriage. William Deere argues in his book Jason's troubled history, the motive, the opportunity, and the physical capability of Jason Simpson all align better with the evidence than O.J. Simpson's involvement.
His
Speaker 21: book suggests O.J. may have even helped cover up Jason's crime to protect his son.
Jason was born in
Speaker 21: 1970. He had a long and documented struggle
Speaker 20: with rage issues. He was diagnosed with intermittent explosive
Speaker 24: disorder and possibly Jekyll and Hyde syndrome. Jason abused drugs and alcohol and had a history of violence. His history included assaults with knives,
Speaker 21: which have obvious parallels to the murders of Nicole Brown Simpson and Ron Goldman.
Speaker 21: Jason worked as a chef at a restaurant near where Ron Goldman was employed, which creates
Speaker 20: an intriguing potential link between the two. On June 12, 1994, the date of the murders, Jason had invited Nicole and their
Speaker 21: children to
dinner at
Speaker 21: his place. Nicole declined. She
instead ate
Speaker 21: at Ron Goldman's restaurant. This rejection amid Jason's unstable mental state
Speaker 21: William Deere argues, could have triggered rage.
Deere claims
Speaker 21: Jason
Speaker 25: had a time card alibi.
But Deere
Speaker 25: compellingly argues that
Speaker 20: the time card showing Jason was
at work
Speaker 20: was in fact fabricated. Fellow employees at Jason's restaurant agree he was not at the restaurant when the time card stated he was.
As a
Speaker 20: result, if Deere is correct, Jason's whereabouts that night are in fact unverified.
The
Speaker 20: black knit cap found at the scene contained dog hairs. The dog hairs were consistent
with dog hairs
Speaker 20: from an Akita. Jason owned an Akita. The unidentified fingerprints at the scene matched no one else that they tested. But Deere argues they could have fit Jason's fingerprints.
and the
Speaker 20: timeline more loosely fits Jason. Jason lives nearby. He could have arrived at Bundy around 1015. He could have committed the acts in a fit of rage or drug-fueled fury and fled without the time constraints faced by O.J. Simpson. Jason's Jeep Cherokee had bloodstains. He
had a
Speaker 20: knife set that had a blade missing that matched the wounds. William Deere allegedly found in
one of
Speaker 20: Jason's storage units We'll be right back.
A
Speaker 20: knife with possible blood residue? Jason's psychiatric records show prescriptions for Depakote, which is prescribed for rage, and a history of threatening suicide with knives. A
note from Jason
Speaker 20: to OJ after the murder read cryptically, possibly
Speaker 22: confessing guilt.
oj's
Speaker 22: supporters point
Speaker 20: to his actions as paternal protection oj hired a dream team of top lawyers but he did not pursue any other suspects during the bronco chase oj drafted what appears to be a final note to the world before he departs and begs the press to leave his children alone in a 2006 book that served as a hypothetical confession written by oj titled if i did it
OJ described a
Speaker 20: companion at the scene. Some interpreted that companion as Jason. Critics dismissed this as speculative, lacking DNA ties. Ultimately, the theory posits OJ's acquittal stemmed from doubt, but true guilt might actually lie with Jason, shielded by family loyalty and a flawed
Speaker 24: investigation. While unproven, it offers a compelling alternative.
Speaker 24: humanizing the tragedy as a father's sacrifice. And that
Speaker 26: is your opening statement. I myself believe that, by the way. I didn't just say all that. I
find it to be
Speaker 26: compelling. I
find it to be compelling. Now, with all that said, the opening
Speaker 18: last night,
the opening
Speaker 28: tonight, Thank
Speaker 2: you.
Both
Speaker 28: were about timelines and how timelines were important to guilt or innocence. And
how it was the
Speaker 28: discovery of the timelines that
led the
Speaker 29: investigation. We're
going to look
Speaker 29: tonight at a detailed timeline of the day of
Charlie
Speaker 2: Kirk being taken out.
Speaker 2: We looked a little bit at a timeline last night, and we're going to refresh ourselves on that timeline tonight. That was the airplanes.
Tonight, we're
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): going to look not only at the flight log timeline, which I will pull back up now so
you can
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): get a good, hard look
at it
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): before we switch
Speaker 2: the audio in case
you did not
Speaker 2: have your phone
handy when I
Speaker 2: showed it the first time or did not get a screen cap. This is the new timeline that I
Speaker 30: believe is compelling.
I don't know if this
Speaker 30: is fact.
But
Speaker 30: this, to me, makes more sense. It's the only timeline that explains this yellow flight right here, this N560 Tango Whiskey
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): flight. If it takes Erica to Provo, repositions to Santa Barbara to get Andrew, and then takes Andrew to Scottsdale, this explains a lot to me. It
also explains
Speaker 28: Andrew would be flying without his cell phone in all likelihood because Andrew's cell phone would want to have it look like he is in
Santa Barbara. So Andrew's wife
Speaker 5: would bring his cell phone here at this 4.36 p.m. landing down here, fourth from the bottom, which
is why Andrew
Speaker 2: would have told people he was a nervous wreck on the flight in because he wouldn't have had an outlet to talk to anybody. He wouldn't have had an outlet to get
any
Speaker 22: information. He would have been on
a flight
Speaker 22: with no devices.
So this is an
Speaker 22: interesting timeline. We're going to come
Speaker 24: back to this.
But I
Speaker 24: want to go tonight to, I'm trying to think of the
Speaker 31: best way to start this. And I think the best way to show this is to kind
of give you
Speaker 1: an overall idea of where we're taking this and then back it out and go line by line. I think that if
Speaker 7: you guys can see an overview
of where
Speaker 7: we're headed.
Yeah, I think that's the best
Speaker 32: way to do it. Let me do this.
I'm going to play
Speaker 32: a lot
Speaker 2: of audio tonight.
You're just going to
Speaker 2: have to deal with it. All of you people who don't like audio are just going
to have
Speaker 2: to
Speaker 3: deal with it. And the reason I'm saying you're going to have to deal with it is because it's important. It's absolutely critical to understanding this story. If
we
Speaker 30: cannot get the audio right, if we cannot figure out what was happening on the ground that day, then we're going to get lost in everything and we're
going
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): to lose everything.
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): I don't want to say
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): the forest for the trees, but we're going to lose a firm understanding of where everybody was and when. So I'm going to start playing some audio here.
Let me bring this
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): column in just
Speaker 35: there. I'm going to start playing some audio here. This is audio
Speaker 31: from 1223, 1223. Let me
pull it
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): up.
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): 12-23, this is the minute, the very minute,
that
Speaker 37: Charlie Kirk heard the Big Bang. We all heard the Big Bang. The Big Bang heard around the
Speaker 38: world. So I'm going to play this audio. This is the first dispatch broadcast that was played that
Speaker 39: night, that afternoon.
You're going to
Speaker 39: hear Alpha 35, we have shots fired. Charlie Kirk is down.
Alpha 34, we
Speaker 40: have shots fired. Charlie Kirk is down.
so that is
Speaker 41: alpha
Speaker 1: 34 we have shots fired charlie kirk is down that that radio call went out at 12 23 that's consistent and why i play that is i'm letting you
Speaker 2: know that our timeline is correct so when we play the rest of these they're all relative to that first dispatch so if we know exactly the second charlie kirk went down and we do believe we know that it was around 12 23 and 30 seconds give or take if we know that
we
Speaker 2: now can build off of that timeline as we play the
rest of
Speaker 2: these recordings.
Here is a
Speaker 42: recording saying he's on his way to the hospital. This is 30 seconds
Speaker 43: later, and this is consistent with what you guys saw. Hey,
we did have
Speaker 44: shots fired. He's on his way to the ambulance. He's on his way to the hospital.
Engine 31 and medic
Speaker 45: ambulance 35.
Speaker 46: respond to a known incident type at three off in utah value on fire two i
don't know if you
Speaker 47: heard that it was breaking up in my ear uh but he says hey we did have shots fired
Speaker 1: he's on his way to the ambulance on his way to the hospital now here's a critical uh
Speaker 23: play here because just seconds after that broadcast just seconds after that broadcast
you're
Speaker 23: This was when we all took a deep sigh of relief because we thought they had the perpetrator. This is the broadcast announcing that they have, in
Speaker 48: fact, captured or arrested a suspect. This was the George Zinn arrest, but here's the audio.
Three in a second, clear and
Speaker 49: respond to SSUVU and an active shooter.
Alpha
Speaker 50: 11, I've got one in custody. Copy,
one in
Speaker 51: custody.
Yeah,
Speaker 24: so Alpha 11 got one in custody and then the dispatcher says copy one in custody. That took place a minute, seven seconds after the initial broadcast. A minute, seven seconds after the initial broadcast. Now, this
is an
Speaker 24: interesting one because it confirms
Speaker 52: what we heard from Brian Harpole in the
Speaker 2: Sean Ryan interview that they were flying up the highway with Charlie Kirk actually hanging out of the
with
Speaker 2: Charlie Kirk actually
Speaker 24: hanging out of the car. This is confirmation of that over the police radio. He says, 212, everybody get off the radio. I've got a black SUV northbound on Wolverine Way. Passenger door is open. Someone trying to hang out of it.
212,
Speaker 53: everybody get off the radio. I've
got a black SUV
Speaker 53: northbound on Wolverine Way. Passenger
Speaker 54: door is open. Someone's trying to hang out
of it.
That
Speaker 55: broadcast right there was
less than
Speaker 8: four minutes after the Big Bang. So they had already gotten Charlie Kirk from the scene of the
Speaker 2: incident into the SUV and were flying up the highway with someone hanging out of the car.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): so here is a bit of confusion our first little bit of confusion that enters this is where they think they have another victim because of
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): someone else hanging out of the car
i
Speaker 54: assume possibly another victim they've got one hanging out of the car so
there
Speaker 57: was some confusion there
Speaker 25: hey maybe maybe we have a second victim why are people hanging out of the car
I
Speaker 25: understand Charlie's a big guy. I do understand that.
And I
Speaker 18: understand when you're initially putting him in, it's going to be difficult to get a six-foot, four-inch Charlie Kirk into the car sideways. But
you would think as
Speaker 20: they're flying
Speaker 26: up the highway, at some point somebody would bend his
legs and close the
Speaker 26: door. I
would
Speaker 58: think.
I would
Speaker 58: think, but
we have yet
Speaker 24: another broadcast discussing someone hanging out of the car. This is a third broadcast
Speaker 59: that someone's hanging out of the car.
Speaker 60: Copy, 2530. In
a vehicle,
Speaker 60: 50 South,
Speaker 61: 1200 West, in Orem, they have one hanging out of the car. We're not sure if they're a patient
or if
Speaker 61: they're just trying to get out of the area.
So
Speaker 18: this is an inner bit, a little bit of confusion, again, that...
And this could
Speaker 62: be somebody fleeing the scene of the crime. You
might have somebody
Speaker 62: fleeing the scene of the crime. And so you can understand where the police are in this situation saying, well, do we pull this car over? Are we slowing it down on the way to the hospital and someone
might have
Speaker 62: been wounded? Or do we let them go, assuming it's the victim? Or do we
pull it
Speaker 62: over, assuming it might be someone trying to get out of the car?
Now, if you
Speaker 62: wonder, and
Speaker 63: as I have,
If you
Speaker 63: wonder if the finishing off, and this
Speaker 1: is a dark, twisted, drab way to think about this, and I hate to even raise the issue, but
I have to
Speaker 1: because I've mentioned it, that there could
Speaker 27: have been a fatal incident inside the car.
Speaker 64: My working hypothesis is that Charlie Kirk was not just...
Speaker 64: taken down
Speaker 65: one way they
would they
Speaker 65: would never have left it as a
they would never have
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): left it up to a single gunshot from the losi center 142 yard gunshot that they just hoped was fatal if you're going to take someone down you're going to make sure they're taken down and we know they made sure they were taken down because
they're
I hate to
Speaker 66: be dark about
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): it, but they didn't have any plan. They didn't have security plans the next day.
Nobody had flight
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): plans the next day. I mean, it just seems obvious to me that it was a plan. It
was a
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): group plan to make sure he didn't make it out of there
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): alive. And
so I've raised
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): the issue of perhaps there was some electricity involved. Perhaps there was something that exploded under his shirt or shocked him under his shirt or some sort of activity under the shirt that caused the shirt to move like that.
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): maybe
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): that he was, you know, there were two small puncture wounds it looks like or wounds of some sort on his arm. Maybe he was hit with a taser or maybe he was hit with a hypodermic needle on his arm.
And then
Speaker 24: of course we were told about the broken vertebrae. I wondered, did they, when
did that happen? Did they do that
Speaker 27: in the car?
You know, make
Speaker 27: sure he's incapacitated, get him in the car and then, I
don't know.
In
Speaker 16: other words, it raises the possibility that he was uncooperative. I
hate to say it, but
Speaker 16: I have to at least mention it because this is like a 10 or 12 minute
ride to
Speaker 16: the hospital.
This is a long ride to the
Speaker 69: hospital. It wasn't right next door. You're driving at highway speeds.
why is
Speaker 69: someone hanging out of the car? Fold
his legs up
Speaker 69: and
Speaker 70: shut the door. It
doesn't make sense to
Speaker 70: me. So I think this is important evidence that
at least
Speaker 42: whatever was happening in the car
needs to be
Speaker 42: evaluated, needs to be examined. Maybe that's why the car was removed so quickly from the fleet of the rental fleet. Maybe
Speaker 71: that's why the car was cleaned and detailed and sold so quickly. I don't know.
I
Speaker 71: don't know. I can't. All I can do is speculate because they've done such a lousy job of preserving the evidence. If we
had the
Speaker 71: evidence, we wouldn't have to speculate.
Speaker 42: Now, would we?
This is
Speaker 42: 1228. So this is five full minutes after the Big Bang. And
they're still
Speaker 35: not to the hospital. He's still hanging out of the car. Here is
how the
Speaker 35: dispatcher words
it.
Speaker 62: so apparently at some point a an officer or ambulance or something has joined the parade oh
my gosh no i didn't do
Speaker 72: it no stop it you didn't see it everybody back up act like it didn't happen
act like it
Speaker 72: didn't happen it was
Speaker 73: a five second clip we're gonna forget about it we're among friends stop it
i pulled
Speaker 71: an ian
Speaker 54: Thank
Speaker 75: you
for listening.
i knew i
Speaker 71: shouldn't have lowered it i knew it as soon
as i
Speaker 71: lowered it i was like you're gonna forget to put it back all right here we go this raises the possibility um well
i'll just
Speaker 74: play it and then we'll
talk about it
Speaker 54: so now somebody else has
Speaker 75: joined the parade
You
Speaker 75: have you have a either an ambulance or
Speaker 10: a police officer that is caught up to the car and is driving with him.
Now, put that in context of this
Speaker 76: next dispatch. One
Speaker 77: other with me at Tempanogos Hospital, please. He
said, I'm going to
Speaker 13: need another one with me at Tempanogos Hospital, please.
Speaker 12: I've not asked these people what all this means. I don't have access to the police officers. They would never talk about an ongoing
Speaker 13: investigation. But
as I look at
Speaker 13: this, I start to put this together. I was like, okay, we have shots fired. Charlie Kirk is down. They've
got one in
Speaker 71: custody. So they're not, I don't think they're worried at this point anyway about people getting away. That's a huge red flag for me.
Speaker 71: because I think this highlights the criticality of George Zinn doing what he did. It allowed anyone else on campus to get away scot-free because the police thought they had the guy. The police were arresting somebody. It took multiple officers to respond. They're no longer looking for people. And this all happened within
Speaker 2: 45 seconds of
the Big Bang. Then you've
Speaker 2: got this SUV flying down the highway.
The passenger
Speaker 75: door is open. Someone's trying to hang out of it.
it does
Speaker 75: not say someone's feet
Speaker 10: are dangling out of it.
Someone's trying to
Speaker 78: hang out of it. That indicates like there's a whole person perhaps. And if you're driving at high-low speed, you might not want to jump out, even if you perceive as
Speaker 18: danger inside the car. All
right, so now
Speaker 12: we've got, we're
going to fast forward a
Speaker 12: little bit because now we're going up to 12.33 p.m., 10 minutes.
Speaker 12: 10 minutes, only 10 minutes past the Big Bang.
And now we
Speaker 12: get the introduction of canine dogs on the
Speaker 79: scene. Here we go.
Speaker 80: 1J,
Speaker 81: 129. I've got all county canines headed that way. Where do you need us? I've
got all county
Speaker 82: canines
Speaker 75: headed that way. Where do you need us? I
don't know what canine
Speaker 75: dogs are looking for in this moment.
I don't
Speaker 75: know what they're looking for. I don't know what they're talking about. I don't know what
Speaker 12: they're after. This is only 10 minutes afterwards. Maybe they just think, hey, we might have a foot chase. We might have, you know, who knows? I don't know what all canines can do. I know
what canines
Speaker 12: allegedly couldn't do, which was locate the rifle. We'll talk about that in a little bit.
So they have these
Speaker 52: canines. They're headed that way. Where do you need us? Now here is...
the
Speaker 35: first indication something is amiss. You've got somebody here who just spoke to a student. What did this student say? Spoke
to a
Speaker 83: student, said that the shooter is on top of the building on the far north side of maybe the
Speaker 84: CS building or
just east of the
Speaker 84: library. He's wearing jeans, black shirt, black mask, long rifle. The
rifle is
Speaker 85: visible.
Speaker 35: Just
spoke to a
Speaker 35: student.
She said
Speaker 35: the shooter is on top of the building on the far north side. I'm
going to
Speaker 35: pull up the building she was just talking about.
She said the CS
Speaker 35: building. That's the computer science building. I'll
show you the building
Speaker 35: we're talking about.
She didn't say the Lossie Center
Speaker 86: building. She said the CS building.
Let me pull this up and give
Speaker 35: you a good idea here of Thank you.
Speaker 35: what we are looking at. This is the CS building.
So if we drill
Speaker 87: in here, we get a, where is the, this is the courtyard, UVU
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): courtyard right here.
This is the UVU
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): courtyard. North is straight up. This is not positioned to the north. I mean, the map is positioned to the north. The courtyard is
Speaker 24: actually kind of east, northeast facing.
but if you back
Speaker 17: up here, this is where we're told the shot was taken from. This is where we're told the shooter came from.
This is not
Speaker 17: the building that that student just said she saw a shooter on. She described a shooter with some particularity.
She described
Speaker 66: the shooter as wearing black jeans, black shirt, black mask, long
Speaker 1: rifle.
And on
Speaker 1: top of the CS
Speaker 88: building, that building is back here. That's a different building. That's this building. And
she says the shooter is
Speaker 17: on top of the building. Just spoke to a student. This is 10 minutes later. Just spoke to a student. Shooter is on this building. I
have long suspected somebody was
Speaker 89: back there acting as a lookout of the whole
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): operation.
And I
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): thought this guy was probably a lookout or a decoy, one or the other. But we'll just allow that for now. So let's go back to our timeline real fast. Let's go back to our timeline.
Speaker 30: Now, we
have yet another
Speaker 30: person describing what
they are
Speaker 30: seeing. We had that person say, shooters in the building wearing long, on top of the building wearing jeans,
black
Speaker 41: shirt black vest we know for a fact that is not what tyler robinson was alleged to have been wearing we have more here
all units
Speaker 90: responding to you you just be advised we have information that the shooter is on top of the building on the far north side just east of the
Speaker 91: library wearing jeans black shirt black vest we are
far north side just
Speaker 92: east of the library
Well, let
Speaker 42: me show you where this is, because this is, again, not anywhere near the Losey Center. This
is your
Speaker 42: library right here.
The far north side,
Speaker 86: this is the north side of campus. Just east is going to be perhaps
Speaker 35: the ROTC building. Perhaps this building, the Sorenson Center building.
But I
Speaker 35: don't know how you would say that this building down here in the middle of campus is on the far north side, just
east of
Speaker 35: the library. This is the library, just east of the library is here. Or perhaps they're situated wrong and they're thinking this is just east of the library. But either way, that's not consistent with,
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): like, why would you use the landmark, the library as a landmark for a building that's in the middle of campus? It doesn't
Speaker 93: make sense.
That doesn't
Speaker 93: make sense. But again, early reports...
Maybe
Speaker 93: things go wrong.
Speaker 24: So let's go back to the timeline and
see if that
Speaker 24: gets
Speaker 41: cleared up at all in any capacity whatsoever, because we have another description here.
The last known location
Speaker 90: I have is that the shooter was on top of the north building just east of the library wearing jeans, black shirt, and
Speaker 91: a vest.
It doesn't
Speaker 48: clear that up any. It's the same exact description,
Speaker 87: same exact thing. This is what they're operating with at this time. Now, let's go forward to...
Ah, this is the
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): key. This is probably one of the more important audio clips we'll play tonight. Let
me cue it
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): up, and then I'm going to say something before I play it.
Oh, that's not
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): right.
All
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): right, let me cue it up, and then I'm going to say something before I play it. I'm going to bring it down. I will
bring it
Speaker 28: back up before I play it.
One of the keys that we've been
Speaker 28: told this entire time is
that we know Tyler Robinson
Speaker 10: was the one on that roof
because while
Speaker 10: he didn't leave a weapon up there, he did leave the screwdriver. The screwdriver was up there.
on the
Speaker 10: Losi Center. We
thought to
Speaker 10: ourselves, well, how
does
Speaker 28: that work? Because at first they told us he reassembled the gun after he got done. Well, you can't reassemble the gun if you don't have a screwdriver. Then they told us, no, the gun was never
Speaker 22: disassembled to need to be reassembled. Okay, well, this is odd. Why did you say it was disassembled and then needed to be reassembled if it didn't need to be reassembled because it
was
Speaker 96: never disassembled? Why did you say that? Then we were told, does it matter
Speaker 10: We don't need to talk about the gun because we found the screwdriver. He left it where he was laying. It was right there. That's how we knew it was his screwdriver.
Let me tell you what
Speaker 10: the first
Speaker 96: officer responding to the scene of
Speaker 13: the crime discovered.
Because I think he will
Speaker 13: disagree with that analysis. And the TPUSA fed slop has fed us a healthy dose of
But
Speaker 13: the screwdriver.
Speaker 97: Listen to what he says.
On
Speaker 98: top of the low-seat building, I do have kind of an imprint,
Speaker 99: which would
be a great angle. Just in 14,
Speaker 99: I'm up on top of the low-seat.
Did you hear anything about a
Speaker 100: screwdriver? Don't
you think
Speaker 100: if he saw a screwdriver? He says
Speaker 88: he sees the imprint. That was an imprint. It would have made a nice angle. I
just have a
Speaker 88: feeling he would have said...
and there's a
Speaker 101: weird screwdriver right here. What's this doing here? I don't know. Maybe I'm
reading
Speaker 102: that too much into it. Now, have you been told that within 24 minutes of the Big Bang, within 24 minutes of the
Speaker 9: Big Bang, that the police already had an image, a still image,
as
Speaker 9: well as a full video in their
Speaker 2: possession. Now, we knew a day or two later somebody came out because they put that thing on X that had the guy lying there on the full video on the thing. We know a day or two later they had the, a couple
of days
Speaker 71: later, they had the surveillance footage from the computer science building that was
looking out
Speaker 71: over the Lossie Center. The FBI released that.
We
Speaker 71: know a day or two later, they came out with the image of everybody
Speaker 3: dropping and somebody noticed, hey, way in the background, there's a little guy that looks like he's scampering off the building. So we knew that
like
Speaker 12: days later.
Was anyone aware? And
Speaker 23: if they were, can we please take a look at this still photo and video? Because the Utah County police, the police scanner.
says
Speaker 42: that they have somebody with a picture and a full video. I don't know if that... Now, maybe they're talking about the actual
Speaker 17: wound, but I mean, I
kind of
Speaker 17: read it as they have an image of the suspect. That's what they're looking for. But you tell me what you hear.
201, can
Speaker 103: you send me a picture of the individual
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): we're looking for? So
that's the
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): response to it. Let me
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): go back to the...
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): them saying they have a video so if he responds saying can you send me a picture it's
in response
Speaker 7: to this transmission we
Speaker 105: have somebody with a picture we have somebody with
a full
Speaker 105: video one
j one thirty two if we
Speaker 106: can get a few more units over to the low-key center to help clear it out
so they the
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): first broadcast was we have somebody with a picture we have somebody with a full video in response to that somebody says well can you send me a picture of the individual what we're looking for?
So at
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): least he
Speaker 17: interpreted it that way as well, that somebody had an image of the person they're looking for. I would like to see that. Who were they looking for?
Now we go back up on top of the
Speaker 42: Lossie Center roof. Now we're doing a little more thorough investigation. Listen for
a
Speaker 107: screwdriver. Do you hear a screwdriver here? I've
got an imprint of a
Speaker 108: body laying. Knee, head, looks like elbow, so somebody with thumb was right here.
Speaker 109: so
Speaker 110: he's
Speaker 42: he's examining the scene closely enough to say i see knees i see legs i see what looks like an elbow so somebody was laying right here any casings i do not see a casing
Speaker 12: but it's straight on
I just
Speaker 12: feel like at that point, he would say, no, I don't see casings, but I see
Speaker 111: this random screwdriver still laying up here. That's weird. So,
again, last time before we leave
Speaker 35: this particular set of audio,
last
Speaker 1: time here, what are we looking for, Madam Dispatcher? Who is our
Speaker 58: suspect? Please, we're waiting with bated breath. Please tell us who we're looking for.
Copy.
The
Speaker 112 (higher-pitched voice): suspect is going to be wearing all black, black long guns, black tactical helmet, a black mask, possibly wearing a tactical vest and jeans. Yep,
we're
Speaker 113: still looking. We're 42, what are we, yeah, 40, almost 50 minutes after the Big Bang. We're
still
Speaker 63: looking at this point
for a
Speaker 63: suspect wearing all black guns.
Speaker 63: black long gun, black tactical helmet, black mask, possibly wearing a tactical vest and jeans. Well, no, you guys say, well, it's possible in the fog of war that people just make mistakes. It's possible in the fog of war, somebody had a miscalculation and they saw a guy that looked like Tyler Robinson running off the
Speaker 42: roof
Well,
Speaker 42: we've all seen Tyler Robinson by now, right? We all know what he looks like. There's nobody in America
Speaker 52: who would say that the Tyler Robinson that they've seen could be described as having shoulder-length hair, for example,
Speaker 86: or aviator sunglasses, right? Nobody would describe anybody as wearing shoulder-length hair
Speaker 35: with aviator sunglasses, so
he's
Speaker 35: Let's hear who they are looking for. If I can get this, there we go.
If I
Speaker 35: can get it nailed down just right
Speaker 52: over the timestamp here. So this is, again, back to the Utah police scanner. We're switching feeds here, so it's going to look
a little
Speaker 52: different on your end, but it's a scanner. So here we go. This was at 1.33 p.m. and 29 seconds, about an
hour and
Speaker 52: 10 minutes after the Big Bang. Who is it you're
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): looking for?
The
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): dispatcher, please, by all means, you have the floor.
Copy mail, dressed in
Speaker 115: all black, swirling hair, aviator glasses, black bag, and a long gun.
So we have a male
Speaker 100: dressed in all black. Now we've added a descriptor because we had, or two descriptors. We had the dressed in all black,
We
Speaker 100: had the, actually, I don't know that we've had anybody mention a long gun to this point. So now we've added a long gun. We've added a black bag. We've added aviator glasses, wherever
Speaker 116: those came from.
And we've
Speaker 116: introduced hair. We've introduced hair.
And lest you think that's the
Speaker 100: only transmission dealing with hair, I will play yet another one about a minute
later.
so
Speaker 100: that you
Speaker 73: guys can see no no no in fact uh
hair has
Speaker 73: become intrinsic to
Speaker 117: this we get it queued up it's
Speaker 118 (lower-pitched voice): pushing in 10 second increments here so let
me let it
Speaker 118 (lower-pitched voice): roll for just a second before i switch over there but keep in
Speaker 119: mind we're listening for hair here we go you ready
Speaker 120: black long pants
Speaker 121: black legs longer hair in the brink shirt sunglasses with a long gun
Speaker 122: Alright, we have a male suspect, black long pants, black
Speaker 12: bag, longer hair, mid-length, dark aviator style sunglasses with a long gun.
As you were listening to the fed slot narrative
Speaker 123: being spoon-fed to you, being crammed down your
throat
Speaker 23: day after day,
Speaker 23: Asking like this was an open and shut case and we had nothing to talk about and we're all just conspiracy theorists.
Do you remember
Speaker 23: anybody talking to you about a suspect with long hair, shoulder length hair, mid length hair?
Does this guy look
Speaker 124: familiar to you? Do you know who this is?
This picture was taken less than a
Speaker 125: week ago.
this is
Speaker 125: alleged
Speaker 23: to be Lance Twiggs. Photographed by the Daily Mail in Texas. That, to me, looks
a lot like the
Speaker 23: description. Now, that's the Lance Twiggs we've all seen. We
never got to
Speaker 23: see his hair, did we? Because they always showed us Lance Twiggs either in a hat or with his stupid costume on.
They never
Speaker 126: one time showed us Lance Twiggs looking like this. This
is the
Speaker 126: first I got to see Lance
Speaker 23: Twiggs. So
when you look in
Speaker 25: the timeline, the timeline
becomes pretty
Speaker 25: important. The
timeline starts to become
Speaker 20: problematic for the prosecution, starts to become problematic for the Fed slot.
We're going to
Speaker 62: get to why, but one of the major kinks
Speaker 25: in the timeline is the introduction to the timeline of a descriptor that looks
a whole
Speaker 25: lot more like
the
Speaker 127: roommate than it does Tyler Robinson.
It
Speaker 12: also might help explain why the
Speaker 10: aunt, interviewed by Brandy and Billy, said that
he
Speaker 12: might have been sort
of being
Speaker 12: coddled a little bit by law enforcement, that
he wasn't
Speaker 12: cooperating, but he sure never was arrested.
So this
Speaker 92: becomes a problem if you are pushing the Fedslop
Speaker 13: narrative. If you're Kash Patel, if
you're the Utah County
Speaker 13: Sheriff's Office, if you're the Utah County Attorney's Office, the introduction of
Speaker 12: a description that matches a mysterious figure who
allegedly is not
Speaker 12: cooperating with you.
Speaker 12: According to his family, that's
an Infiniti
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): FX35. I've seen about 10 people ask who the car is.
But if you, you
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): know, let's
just say
Speaker 7: you're Jack Posobiec, right? Jack Posobiec went around and for like
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): 100 days, we're like four or five months into this thing. But for like 100 straight days, Jack Posobiec.
was
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): probably the
Speaker 47: strongest advocate for the Fed Slop theory.
And, oh, it was so
Speaker 97: easy. He confessed in text messages.
Speaker 129: He told his parents he did it. No, no, no, no, no, friends. It's
starting to
Speaker 129: look to me like
Speaker 29: this Lance Twiggs may have played a larger role than we're being told.
Speaker 29: God love our British
Speaker 1: journalists from the Daily Mail because without them, we would not know Lance Twiggs looks like this.
We would have been spoon-fed the Fed Slop
Speaker 1: narrative and the Fed Slop pictures of Lance Twiggs with short hair.
and we would have
Speaker 126: been stuck with that. That's all we would have had. He was kind of a mysterious figure. He didn't have a huge online presence. But
that, to
Speaker 126: me, looks
Speaker 130: precisely like
what we
Speaker 130: were told in that description. Looks
a lot like it
Speaker 131: to me.
And
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): there's something in the law, this Brady evidence, right? You guys know what Brady evidence is? I'm not suggesting this is Brady
Speaker 132 (lower-pitched voice): evidence, but I'm not suggesting the defense doesn't have this. I have it. I'm assuming they have it.
But the reason Brady evidence
Speaker 86: exists is if there's something exculpatory, meaning if there's some evidence
Speaker 24: that points to someone else having done it, you're entitled to
Speaker 78: have it and evaluate it.
you're
Speaker 78: entitled to review it, you're entitled to test it, you're entitled to follow up on it.
And if the defense is
Speaker 35: entitled to it, then we as the public, if we're looking at this and drawing conclusions and speculating, nobody should be calling us conspiracy
Speaker 88: theorists. No,
no, you
Speaker 88: guys have been hiding from us this entire time.
that there's a
Speaker 88: description that fits the roommate, and we don't know where the roommate was. And the roommate had really bizarre
Speaker 133: phone call, text messages back and forth with Tyler Robinson that basically fried Tyler Robinson. And
the roommate might
Speaker 133: have also had access to his
Speaker 22: Discord chat, his computer. Remember
how he confessed
Speaker 22: to everything on Discord?
I want
Speaker 134: to play one more clip from this scanner here, if I can get it dialed in just right. Oh,
just
Speaker 24: about nailed it.
Let me go
Speaker 78: back. Watch how I share the screen and don't accidentally play it to myself while you guys all sit around wondering what the hell I'm doing. You see how I've done this? I brought it up.
I brought it up. Let me play one
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): more clip from this particular scanner.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): Again, this is from 1.36 p.m. and 51 seconds.
This is somebody
Speaker 59: relaying once again the description. I've
got the
Speaker 135: description you were looking for on the temperature of the mail.
You ready for that? And on your name, the description
Speaker 136: on the
Speaker 137: mail, all in black, long pants, black bag.
Speaker 137: 88 style sunglasses with a long gun
Speaker 138: information
Speaker 135: was given at 13 and 26 copy
Speaker 139: that 301 to all units just 10-14 that information was observed on camera footage an hour prior to it being given
Speaker 140: out wait a minute you're
Speaker 116: telling me an hour before Uh-huh.
Speaker 23: 1326, which would be 1226, which would be two or three minutes after the Big Bang. Two
or three
Speaker 23: minutes after the Big Bang,
there was
Speaker 100: observed camera footage of a male, all in black, long pants, black bag, aviator style
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): sunglasses and a long gun.
Do you see how
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): problematic this is by now? Do
you see how problematic this has
Speaker 142: become? The
Speaker 100: entire slop we were told for the next several days? Keep in mind, the guy who was dressed in black
with aviator
Speaker 100: glasses, the black bag, and the long gun
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): was described by two other dispatches, two separate dispatches, by two different dispatchers,
As
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): having shoulder-length hair, medium hair, long hair.
But we've been told it had to be
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): Tyler
Speaker 144: Robinson. Have you ever seen Tyler Robinson with shoulder-length hair at all? Or aviator sunglasses? Or all in black with a long gun?
Speaker 124: No. I've
seen none
Speaker 124: of that.
where is
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): the camera footage
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): that you supposedly observed three minutes, three minutes after
the Big
Speaker 42: Bang? Two and a half maybe. Because
this is
Speaker 42: 1.36 and 51 is when this went out. He said
the information
Speaker 42: was given at 13.26,
Speaker 23: and that information had been observed on camera an hour before that.
which
Speaker 23: means, ladies and gentlemen, there is
camera
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): footage out there of a man with long hair and aviator sunglasses.
Where is
Speaker 145: it? Where is it? You
want me
Speaker 145: to...
Speaker 146 (higher-pitched voice): Where is it? I
want to know
Speaker 146 (higher-pitched voice): where the camera footage is of the guy in aviator
Speaker 147: glasses and shoulder-length hair.
I've got to
Speaker 148: know. I've
been
Speaker 16: told it exists now by two different dispatchers. Because
I want to know if
Speaker 16: it looks like this. I
want to know if the guy in
Speaker 133: aviator glasses with shoulder-length hair looks a little bit like this. All
Speaker 149: black, black
Speaker 3: bag. You know, the fact that he's carrying a black bag is just poetic here and wearing a black hat.
It
Speaker 3: has shoulder-length hair and
has black
Speaker 150: pants. I mean, the only thing missing is the long gun.
You guys feel lied to
Speaker 151: yet? Do
the text messages
Speaker 151: now make a little more sense in light of the
Speaker 152: Daily Mail's photos that we now have? Do
the text messages
Speaker 152: start to add up a little more to you back and forth?
Speaker 152: Almost as if Lance Twiggs
Speaker 100: is being exonerated by
the text
Speaker 100: messages. Oh,
I didn't even know
Speaker 100: he was in there engraving bullets. I didn't know he was doing any of this. How
Speaker 153: long have you been planning this, my love? A little over a week, my love. I think.
Where is that
Speaker 154: photo? It was observed by photo.
And
Speaker 154: another dispatcher said photo and video
more than
Speaker 6: an hour before the dispatch at 1336. More
than an hour before the original
Speaker 6: dispatch at 1326, which
would have
Speaker 6: been nearly simultaneous.
Who's the conspiracy theorist? Who's the
Speaker 155: conspiracy theorist?
I've got
Speaker 100: a guy who was exonerated by text message in
the minutes
Speaker 100: or hours after the event
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): that seems to identically fit the description. That's weird to me.
It would be as if
Speaker 16: I stole a cookie out of the cookie jar in the kitchen. I walk into
Speaker 6: the kitchen, I steal a cookie.
I eat
Speaker 6: the cookie because cookies are delicious. Who doesn't
love
Speaker 19: cookies? I put
the lid
Speaker 19: neatly back on the cookie jar and I walk away.
Someone walks in the
Speaker 19: kitchen and says, there
were five
Speaker 19: cookies in the cookie jar. Now there are four. Who ate the cookie? And
so they go
Speaker 100: on a hunt. They're looking for crumbs. They're
looking for
Speaker 100: evidence of cookie. They're looking at people's mouths. Do you see
cookie
Speaker 156: dust? Is there cookie dust in your mouth?
And
Speaker 156: you're not talking because you still got crumbs in your mouth. You're like, there's no cookies in here. And you're quickly,
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): you grab your neighbor's phone or
your
Speaker 6: roommate's phone and you start saying, I ate the cookie. I know
you would
Speaker 6: never eat a cookie. You hate cookies. You're
allergic to
Speaker 6: everything in cookies. You can't eat flour. You can't eat milk, eggs. You're anti-cookie. You're an anti-cookite.
you're an anti-cookite, you
Speaker 6: hate cookies,
you would
Speaker 6: never eat the cookie. And
I go back and I say, did you eat
Speaker 16: the cookie? Because
now I have
Speaker 16: my phone, I have both phones. Did
you
Speaker 101: eat the cookie? And my roommate's phone, I grabbed my roommate's phone back and I'm like, it
is
Speaker 19: I, I eateth thy cookie, my love. I've
been
Speaker 6: planning the cookie caper for well over a week.
I just
Speaker 6: couldn't stand looking at their chocolate chip deliciousness any longer.
Don't talk to anyone. Hang up. That's how the text messages
Speaker 158: now read to
Speaker 159: me.
The text messages now read that
Speaker 159: way to me.
I look at this and I
Speaker 70: think, wait a minute.
In broad
Speaker 142: daylight this whole time,
the state
Speaker 142: was looking, the county was looking, the feds were looking for somebody with long hair
and a
Speaker 10: long gun. And
the images they released to us
Speaker 10: were Tyler Robinson decidedly
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): with not long hair. Oh, and they have
picture and
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): video of somebody with long hair and
Speaker 144: aviator glasses
Speaker 160: dressed in all black with a long gun and a black bag.
haven't
Speaker 161: released those to me i haven't seen them i
haven't seen them next next
Speaker 41: uh this next video this next piece of audio was captured and saved thankfully saved because
it is
Speaker 41: impossible to find online now ladies and
Speaker 162: gentlemen it cannot be located online it's that important all
this other
Speaker 162: stuff is still available online this
next piece
Speaker 10: of audio i'm going to play is
gone
Speaker 10: but for a hero like Project Constitution,
Speaker 9: we wouldn't have access to it.
But he
Speaker 9: saved it.
He saved
Speaker 9: it, and we're thankful he did because we
Speaker 41: would not have it today. And
I'm going to
Speaker 41: play it because it's important to our timeline. This
is important
Speaker 52: to our timeline. So I'm going to play this video here from Project Constitution, and it's going to
Speaker 28: illuminate the timeline even further.
This is,
Speaker 28: again, of all the video
Speaker 130: or all the audio that was captured that we have access to, it
was
Speaker 87: gone. This
is gone, and I'll play
Speaker 87: it, and then
I'll tell
Speaker 87: you why I think it's missing.
Am I the only one that
Speaker 163: came here?
Speaker 164: Oh, I did do the request. They emailed
Speaker 165: me back. He did not go in for an autopsy, the death certificate was signed by the doctor at the hospital.
Speaker 166: Okay. Can you just do a clip
Speaker 165: documenting that?
I'm sorry,
Speaker 167: 10-9?
Can
Speaker 166: you
Speaker 168: just add a suck to the case documenting that there was no autopsy? 287, I'll be clear to the hospital. I
need
Speaker 169: an officer at Timpanogos Hospital to come stage in the emergency room bay. Jesse just told
Speaker 170 (lower-pitched voice): me that he just got off the phone and Charlie's wife is coming to signature. I'm going
to pause
Speaker 8: it right there. Jesse's wife called...
Speaker 8: Charlie, or Jesse just called, Charlie's wife is coming to signature. I'm
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): going to pull up
on Google Earth
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): what they're talking about, because this is important
that you
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): guys understand the distinction here at the Provo Airport.
Don't get caught up on the
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): autopsy thing. I've got an explanation for that. We'll talk about it in a second. I want to give you some
ground
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): laying here for the Provo Airport so that you guys understand what we're looking at.
This is
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): the Provo Airport.
there
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): are three ways you can fly into Provo Airport. One way is to fly into the main airport. This is your main airport. This is the Provo Airport main terminal. This is where the poor people fly. This is where the plebs fly. If you, gentle audience, or
Speaker 28: I were
to fly
Speaker 28: into Provo, this
is where we
Speaker 28: would fly.
Speaker 172: We
would fly
Speaker 172: into poor man's land over here.
This is
Speaker 172: for people who make
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): average livings,
who work for a
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): living, who don't have non-profits and billionaires paying them millions of dollars a year.
Speaker 13: Nope. Not those people. It's us.
This is
Speaker 13: where we fly. This is the south end. Over here, you have what's called an FBO. This is
Speaker 30: where rich people fly in.
You'll notice
Speaker 30: the private jets on the plane here. This is called an FBO. This is
Speaker 30: um,
this is
Speaker 87: called signature in Provo. So
if someone
Speaker 87: says they're
Speaker 47: flying into signature, this is where they fly in. Notice how small this parking lot is, right? This is where the elite travel.
The elite
Speaker 47: travel into signature. They
have a little tiny
Speaker 162: parking lot. These are little tiny rental cars down here that you can get.
This is where
Speaker 162: they travel. There's a third way to travel in, believe it or not. You
can fly all
Speaker 5: the way here to the north side,
and you can park
Speaker 5: your rig up here. This
is Duncan
Speaker 19: Aviation. You'll
notice Duncan
Speaker 19: Aviation has their own little rental car lot right here. They've
got their own
Speaker 19: little parking lot up here.
And
Speaker 19: it's a long
Speaker 173: way away. Like
Speaker 5: you would never drive a car down a hot runway, right?
Speaker 89: So you wouldn't drive this way. In order to get from Duncan, you'd have to come back
Speaker 13: out here to the highway, drive about a mile south, and then come in this entrance to Signature or come even farther south and come into the main entrance here to
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): the Provo Airport.
so we
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): know erica is not flying into poor man's land that's not how she travels so
that's not going
Speaker 3: to be erica there so the question we have is is erica coming into signature which is
Speaker 66: right here this is where a lot
of rich
Speaker 66: people fly or is she flying into duncan which
is up
Speaker 66: here where other rich people fly
Right
Speaker 174: there, you had somebody say they just got off the phone with a guy named Jesse, and Jesse said that
Speaker 86: Charlie's wife is coming to Signature. Let's go back and see if
anybody else
Speaker 175: heard anything different from Charlie's wife.
Okay.
so he just
Speaker 22: taught he just up talk now that is not an
Speaker 17: erica kirk up talk that's not like erica you're going charlie's wife is coming to signature no no no no no this is a guy who talks normally like an actual
human being and so when
Speaker 88: he up talks he's asking a question wait
a minute
Speaker 88: charlie's wife is coming to signature why
Speaker 43: would you say
that
Speaker 43: Oh, did I lose the audio? Oh, I pulled a
Speaker 176: Baron again. Let
me pull it back up. I
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): apologize, guys. I know what happened. I
can't go
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): away from the audio and then come back to the audio if it's in Twitter. So I apologize. That's
not pulling a
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): Baron. That's
just me
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): being me. All right. So.
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): Jesse just got off the phone and they're
Speaker 178: coming to signature. Now, let me share it again, and you should have audio this time.
So, Charlie's wife has come to
Speaker 179: signature. Now,
Speaker 180: listen now to
where they go
Speaker 180: from here. Actually, I need to go back, right? Because you guys didn't hear that part.
Jesse
Speaker 181: just told me that he just got
Speaker 170 (lower-pitched voice): off the phone and Charlie's wife is coming to
Speaker 182: signature and to bring in a car over here
for a while.
Speaker 183: Charlie's wife is coming to land a
Speaker 182: signature, you
Speaker 184: said?
Speaker 185: Sir, and Jesse's going to go to Duncan right now and pick up a car for her.
Speaker 186: Okay, you guys have it now, right?
Yeah, we listen and we
Speaker 186: don't judge. We
listen and we
Speaker 6: don't judge. So, Jesse, you still didn't hear it? Or is it the second one?
If
Speaker 6: not, I'm
Speaker 187: just going to read it because the words are on the screen. I'll just read it out loud to you.
So, Jesse is saying she is
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): coming. Okay, so I can't tell if there's no... Some of you are behind and some of you are ahead. So, all good now. Thank you. Okay. Jesse is saying she's
coming to
Speaker 8: signature. That's the middle of the three options.
Speaker 8: At the south end, you have poor man's land. That's where you guys and Mrs. Coleman and I might fly in.
In the middle,
Speaker 8: we have Signature.
Speaker 13: That's where a lot of rich people fly in. And at the very top, we have Duncan.
Duncan
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): Aviation, D-U-N-C-A-N. I know it translated on the AI transcription to D-U-N-K-I-N, like Dunkin' Donuts. But we're not going to Dunkin' Donuts. We're going
Speaker 12: to Duncan Aviation, perhaps.
so
Speaker 12: jesse must be one of these guys that works for the police because this is or the fire this is a police and fire dispatch now
let wait till you hear
Speaker 12: this next
Speaker 1: line and this is why i think this is no longer available this is why we can't find it this
Speaker 6: is why i said god save project constitution he's out here doing the lord's work because of this
next line
Speaker 189: okay i'm a little confused because core that's what corey just said they said they're landing at duncan so
I
Speaker 189: don't know where they're landing, but we will just
Speaker 190: kind of play it by ear, I guess, best that we can.
So, Corey, I don't
Speaker 25: know who
Jesse and Corey
Speaker 25: are, but they work there.
Jesse says they're
Speaker 25: landing at Signature, but I'm going to go over to
Speaker 191: Duncan and get a car for them.
Corey says, no, no,
Speaker 191: no, no, no, they're landing at Duncan.
They're landing at
Speaker 191: Duncan.
I'll show
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): you why this is important. We go back to yesterday. This is why I wanted to do yesterday's show
Speaker 21: before we did tonight's show. This is precisely
why I
Speaker 21: wanted to do them in this order. Because this,
I think,
Speaker 86: is the source of the confusion. This flight down here, this
Speaker 13: N-102 Delta Zulu, Scottsdale to Provo that lands at 312,
Speaker 10: You see how I have Andrew on that flight?
We were
Speaker 10: told, we've been told the whole time, we've been left with the impression all along that that flight contained Erica Kirk.
That flight would have come
Speaker 192: into signature.
that flight would
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): have come in at Signature. I'm going to answer the question of what time that is in just a second. That flight would have come into Signature. On
an ordinary
Speaker 8: track, an ordinary person who flies an ordinary Gulfstream 5 into Provo Airport would
Speaker 6: land at Signature FBO, fixed-based
Speaker 9: operator. That's where they would have landed. But
if I'm
Speaker 9: right,
And
Speaker 9: Erica actually arrived at
Speaker 35: this flight right here, second from the top, this N560 Tango Whiskey. If I'm right about that,
Erica wouldn't have been
Speaker 35: able to hang out at
Speaker 193: Signature from 10.06 a.m. until 3.30 p.m.
Someone would have
Speaker 193: spotted her.
She would have
Speaker 194: had to be at Duncan.
And
Speaker 57: so Corey...
Speaker 57: Whoever Corey is, I don't know who Corey and Jesse are. They work for the police. They work for the fire department. They work
Speaker 19: for somebody who
has
Speaker 13: access to these cops who are going to pick these people up.
Somebody thought she
Speaker 13: was at Duncan.
And there's no
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): explanation for why a N-102 Delta Zulu flight coming in at 3.30, a Gulfstream 5,
Speaker 13: would be landing
at
Speaker 13: Duncan, it would only land as signature. It
would only land at
Speaker 2: signature. That is why I am convinced this timeline has a lot of merit. In my opinion, this timeline has a lot of merit. The
conclusion would
Speaker 2: be,
Speaker 22: if I'm right, if my
opinion is
Speaker 22: correct, the conclusion would be is that Erica
Speaker 2: arrived at 10.06 a.m.
two and a
Speaker 2: half hours before Charlie Kirk was taken down. If
I'm right
Speaker 2: about
Speaker 28: that, it changes the whole narrative. It's no longer Tyler Robinson, the lone gunman on the Losey Center.
But I cannot square
Speaker 4: the fact that
one of
Speaker 4: these officials thought he was
Speaker 1: going to be at Duncan. Unless...
Speaker 1: somebody knew she was going to be at Duncan. Oh, I'm confused because
Speaker 178: Corey said she was at Duncan. Now,
Speaker 195: time. Someone
asked about
Speaker 195: the time. Here's
the dirty
Speaker 195: little
Speaker 28: secret. Because these recordings are no longer available, we don't know what time that was. We
don't know what time
Speaker 129: that was. What we do know is it was after...
Speaker 172: 1.30 and before 5.10.
That's all we
Speaker 172: know. It was in that window after 1.30 p.m. and before 5.10.
My guess is it was close
Speaker 5: to 3.30, and here's why. Because they're keeping
up the
Speaker 5: game, in my opinion. They're keeping up this
Speaker 29: game that she's flying in on this 3.30 flight from Scottsdale.
but
Speaker 9: they screwed up they always screw up the facts always have a way of bubbling to the surface just
Speaker 8: like yesterday we discussed we go back to this for
just a second just like
Speaker 8: yesterday we discussed how
they screwed up
Speaker 10: and they told us that andrew fell into erica's arms on the tarmac
And if you look at
Speaker 30: this timeline, they're telling us Erica's flight was this green flight here that landed in the threes. I think it's supposed to be 3.32 instead of 3.12. But either way, at 3 something p.m., and Andrew's flight was supposed to land here at 4.36 p.m. If
Andrew falls into her
Speaker 96: arms, if what they're telling us is true and Andrew falls into her arms, that means Erica stayed around at the airport for over an hour.
and that's
Speaker 133: nonsense.
Speaker 42: If I'm right, and Andrew flew in on this N-102
Speaker 35: Delta Zulu flight that I have him listed on, because this is all my opinion here, if I'm right
Speaker 30: about that,
Erica would
Speaker 30: have been at that airport for him to fall into her arms when he got off the
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): airplane. And
Erica would not have
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): spotted Andrew's wife because Andrew's wife hadn't come yet.
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): Because Andrew would have been coming alone from Scottsdale.
And so when
Speaker 29: Candace asked Erica, was Andrew's wife on that flight,
Erica was
Speaker 29: very smart.
Because she said she
Speaker 96: didn't know.
Because the consequences of her being
Speaker 96: wrong would have been devastating.
But the only reason she
Speaker 96: wouldn't
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): know is if
she didn't know what
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): the story was.
that's the
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): only way she would have been wrong on this is if she didn't know what
Speaker 10: the story was.
I hope that clears
Speaker 10: stuff up for you on the timeline relative to the planes. I
hope that clears that up
Speaker 30: for you. I have a couple of more pieces of audio I
want to
Speaker 30: play
Speaker 47: because it gets to a
Speaker 52: weird...
Speaker 52: story that we have yet to been told. We were told there was a
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): story of a young man who got arrested. It was the second of the three arrests that Kash Patel announced. The first arrest he announced was George Zinn. And we
learned that
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): that was incorrect. That George Zinn,
Speaker 41: in fact, was not the shooter.
The second arrest
Speaker 41: was a guy named Zechariah Qureshi. Zechariah Qureshi was arrested um
yeah
Speaker 41: about,
I don't
Speaker 41: know, three in the afternoon or so, maybe four in
Speaker 52: the afternoon. And they made a second announcement. Nope, we had the wrong guy the first time,
but now we've got the
Speaker 52: right guy. And
I want to
Speaker 52: play the video here, or the audio, of him getting arrested or them looking for him, because there's a fact in here we
Speaker 86: haven't been told that's very
Speaker 198: bizarre.
Speaker 198: It's just bizarre beyond bizarre. I want to get it queued up exactly right so I'm not wasting your time with a bunch of dead
Speaker 199: air. Here we go. And I don't recall anyone telling me this along the way.
Listen to what the
Speaker 199: dispatcher says
Speaker 134: this guy is doing before they arrest him.
Speaker 200: Okay.
Tactical
Speaker 201: vests in a black mask, possibly carrying a rifle.
Toyota Corolla
Speaker 201: S820 Bravo Lima, suspect, hostile name Zachariah Quershi, date of birth 512-2000. The male is going from hospital to hospital looking for the victim.
The
Speaker 142: male is going from hospital to hospital looking for the victim.
Huh? The male is this Zechariah
Speaker 202: Qureshi that they're looking for. They
just put
Speaker 8: a bolo out on this guy. They
gave his
Speaker 8: date of birth. They gave his license plate number. They gave his height, his weight. Hazel
eyes, blonde
Speaker 9: hair, male.
Speaker 9: Tactical vest, black mask, possibly carrying a rifle. They think it's this guy, Zechariah Qureshi. Why?
Because he's
Speaker 9: going from
Speaker 192: hospital to hospital looking for the victim. What? Why?
Speaker 201: Zero. Notify if located in DHL, 1511. Height,
511,
Speaker 203: 198 pounds. Hazel eyes, blonde
Speaker 204: hair, male.
And a broadcast,
Speaker 204: 1511.
Those also have
Speaker 205: male carrying a black bag with tan straps. Possibly driving a 2016 black Toyota Corolla, 28 Sierra 820 Bravo Lima. Suspect is Zachariah Cresci, 512 of 2000. Male is going hospital to hospital looking
for the victim.
Speaker 206: going hospital to hospital
Speaker 30: looking for the victim two different broadcast two different dispatches saying that we have
a male
Speaker 30: who eventually was arrested that was going hospital to hospital looking for the victim
zechariah
Speaker 130: koreshi hospital hospital
Speaker 88: looking for the victim i don't recall hearing about
that i recall
Speaker 88: hearing he got arrested i recall his name
i
Speaker 88: recall seeing his picture i recall all that but i don't recall hearing him going
Speaker 35: hospital to hospital looking for the victim
and here's another
Speaker 207: dispatch on this guy two
zero
Speaker 208: bravo lima here eight two bravo lima local uh in
Speaker 205: eastbound university parkway
Speaker 209: in orem about
six
Speaker 210: minutes ago
Speaker 209: now correction about 14 minutes ago now no idea on the shooter at this time
Speaker 211: So they're actively looking for this guy. Why?
Speaker 41: Why? Why
are they looking
Speaker 41: for this guy? There's one more set of audio I want to play. This
one has a
Speaker 41: little video. I want
Speaker 212: to pull it all the way back
Speaker 213: to
Speaker 214: here.
Speaker 30: Um,
And
Speaker 30: this is going to give us the FBI telling people to stand down, essentially. Do not interview these people. They want to be the one to
Speaker 199: interview it. Why? It's
a little
Speaker 199: weird to me. You know, the FBI is just disclaiming it now. They're saying,
Speaker 215: oh, that's a state investigation. But
in the
Speaker 215: immediate aftermath, the FBI was all saying things like this.
Speaker 216: 11J50?
Just
Speaker 216: 10-14. I'm still about 15 out, but
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): the 1-2 unit is going to be up there to interview Andrew. As per FBI and FBI, we've been given clear direction not to interview, confirming negative interview until they get there. 1-40,
we were not going to interview.
Speaker 218: We are just arriving now. So
that was at
Speaker 13: 5-15 p.m.?
Speaker 13: at 5.15 p.m. they
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): have somebody I'm assuming it's Qureshi who
was
Speaker 52: going hospital to hospital looking for the victim and they're saying don't interview
Speaker 220: the guy don't interview the guy well why here's some more I
Speaker 221: was just told that the FBI wants you to stand by there with him and they're on their way to you copy will do Yeah.
Thank
Speaker 221: you. That came from the agent
Speaker 190: that's leaving Provo PD right now.
Speaker 222: Okay. So the, the FBI thinks they
Speaker 43: have a suspect. Cash Patel has tweeted to the world that they have arrested somebody
and the FBI is on their way and they
Speaker 223: don't want anyone to interview. Well,
Speaker 223: What happens shortly after
Speaker 30: the FBI arrives? Let's first play one more clip of the FBI getting close. This is 5.36
Speaker 24: p.m.
So now we're
Speaker 24: getting a timeline. I'll tell you why I'm playing these in just a second. We've got to get to this timeline so that you can see what's happening.
Just
Speaker 225: confirming we're not looking for anyone or any vehicles still outstanding, correct?
Okay.
so
Speaker 150: they're they're not looking for any more vehicles they've got a guy they're ready to
go
Speaker 41: the fbi's on the way that
was 5
Speaker 41: 36 p.m the fbi shows up four minutes later what
do they find within
Speaker 41: minutes now keep
Speaker 4: in mind at the time before this broadcast they had bomb dogs they had gun dogs out looking nobody could find anything
You
Speaker 4: remember they
Speaker 226: had the dogs sweeping
Speaker 155: that area right there by the chicken coop. And
they couldn't
Speaker 155: find anything. The dogs could not find anything.
The dogs could not find
Speaker 73: anything. The
FBI shows up, and
Speaker 73: just a couple of minutes later we get this.
Speaker 227: 14, just northeast of a low-sea building, forensics has recovered a weapon.
Speaker 227: 7J-16, do you have traffic for me?
Speaker 228: 7J-14, the forensics team has located a weapon just across the street from Lot Mike 20 near the low-seat building.
Isn't that miraculous? That is
Speaker 101: miraculous to me.
Nobody could find the
Speaker 101: weapon until the FBI showed up.
As soon as they get
Speaker 101: there, they go right to it.
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): don't interview anyone, don't touch anything, we're on our way. We're here now, there's your weapon.
Speaker 230: Huh? How's that work?
How does that
Speaker 231: work? And
let's look at what kind of
Speaker 232: weapon they got, because we have this as well.
Okay.
Speaker 233: Command, can you confirm what type of weapon has
Speaker 170 (lower-pitched voice): recovered? Do you guys have that info?
Speaker 228: Standby, I'll get that info.
Speaker 234: So they're looking for the weapon here. Let's let it roll. It's
going to
Speaker 228: be a rifle of some sort. It was wrapped in a towel. We haven't exposed it yet.
Speaker 236: So the rifle is
just
Speaker 236: tripped over by these
Speaker 28: FBI agents who just showed up. The bomb dogs couldn't find it. The gun dogs couldn't find it. Remember, every canine in the county has been deployed to the scene. They
could not
Speaker 162: find it.
They could not find
Speaker 10: it anywhere. But
when the FBI
Speaker 10: shows up, buddy, right to the gun. Boom! Right to the gun. And
here's a final
Speaker 30: little clip, just so you guys can tell.
that
Speaker 30: maybe we got the wrong guy. Do you
Speaker 39: remember hearing this audio dispatch at any point? Go
Speaker 237: ahead. I've
got an
Speaker 238: individual over here who said she witnessed the shooting, and
it's
Speaker 239: different than what she saw from what the news is saying. She's over here at McDonald's and would like to meet with an officer that would take a report on this. Have
we seen
Speaker 239: the report? Has
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): anyone seen the report from the girl who witnessed the shooting?
And
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): said it's different from what everybody is reporting?
How is it different? What
Speaker 161: did she see? Where is she?
What is
Speaker 161: her name?
What did the
Speaker 161: report say?
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): What did she say? Did
she see
Speaker 143 (higher-pitched voice): someone pull a trigger? Did she see somebody with long hair? Medium hair?
Aviator
Speaker 240: glasses?
Speaker 241: Guys, this is a problem. This
is a
Speaker 241: real problem. All of
this
Speaker 100: is a problem. All
of this is taking
Speaker 152: place in the background. All of this is what we would call evidence. Evidence doesn't mean it's
Speaker 144: Solid, bulletproof, confirmed, tested, cross-examined, and proven to be. No, evidence means
it's
Speaker 100: eyewitness testimony, it's police dispatches, it's recordings. That's all called evidence.
What we have here is evidence
Speaker 88: that the Fed slop narrative we've been given, and keep in mind, this is contemporaneous evidence. This is evidence happening
Speaker 43: in real time.
They're looking for a
Speaker 43: guy with long hair. That's not something you inject.
If you
Speaker 43: didn't see it.
That's not
Speaker 242: something you inject into a witness description if you didn't see it.
And if you've seen the
Speaker 41: images of Lance, excuse me, of Tyler Robinson, Tyler Robinson on campus pictures. If you see the images that the FBI released of Tyler Robinson on campus.
Speaker 41: There's nobody,
Speaker 111: nobody on earth who would conclude that this guy has shoulder-length hair or aviator sunglasses.
Nobody, nor that he's wearing black
Speaker 243: pants or a tactical vest.
there's
Speaker 244: not a single person out there who would say when they saw this guy fleeing from the scene
Speaker 102: would go oh, shoulder length hair shoulder length hair, I saw it it was flapping in the wind like a flag in
a hurricane there's
Speaker 87: also nobody who would look at this and say oh, I see a gun
I see a
Speaker 87: stock, I see a barrel. There's nobody. Not
a single person
Speaker 236: on earth.
You want me to tell
Speaker 236: you my conclusion here, guys?
You've been lied to. You've been lied
Speaker 35: to. And if you've been paying attention to my openings from the last
month,
in
Speaker 1: several days, you'll
see where
Speaker 1: I'm headed. You
remember the Boston
Speaker 1: Marathon bombers? You
remember
Speaker 156: that one? How
a couple
Speaker 156: of months after the Boston Marathon bombing, if you didn't hear the opening, you should
go check
Speaker 156: it out. You remember a
couple of
Speaker 156: months after the Boston Marathon bombing, a guy named Daniel Morley was arrested? And
when Daniel Morley
Speaker 12: was arrested, Yeah.
They
Speaker 13: found in his possession bomb-making materials that were identical to what was used at the scene of the Boston Marathon. And
his mother's
Speaker 22: boyfriend, who lived with him, said, oh, he's had that since before the Marathon bombing.
The official narrative was,
Speaker 10: because we're always fed slop, right? We're always fed, fed slop. The official fed slop coming out of the Boston Marathon bombing was, oh, these guys got radicalized online by Islam.
and you know
Speaker 10: how they are. They just get wilded up online. They're out there wilding out online, and
they were
Speaker 10: reading some online magazine about how to make bombs, and that's where they learned how to make the bombs.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, but why didn't the bomb resemble the bomb-making in the magazine? Because it doesn't look the same. It uses different components.
Speaker 71: It uses different trigger device. It uses different propellant.
That doesn't
Speaker 245: make sense to me. It
makes more
Speaker 245: sense to me that a guy they knew
that
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): had all of the same
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): bomb making material before the boston marathon bomb and who showed evidence that he knew how to put it all together
Speaker 23: makes more sense that guy might have done it
it makes more it
Speaker 23: makes more sense to me that guy might have done it well he gets arrested for a domestic violence case against his mother
and the
Speaker 22: fbi shows
up quickly on
Speaker 22: the scene right away
and the charges
Speaker 22: go away he's never arrested, even though he threatened
Speaker 5: to burn down his house
and
harm
Speaker 5: his mother, make bombs,
even though he confessed
Speaker 5: to doing something that he'll have to answer
to God for, he can only
Speaker 5: answer to God for,
the charges go away. It's weird. Almost like the
Speaker 246: FBI may have known that
Speaker 191: guy.
Almost like the FBI may have
Speaker 191: known that guy.
Why else would
Speaker 191: they have shown up right
away to secure
Speaker 191: the scene?
why else
Speaker 191: would they
Speaker 5: have been involved in a domestic violence call that's weird does the fbi always respond to domestic violence calls probably not so that was that
was an opening
Speaker 5: a few days ago
it's almost like these openings are
Speaker 5: written for a reason then
i did the
Speaker 96: opening on the murtaugh murders in south carolina
and that we were
Speaker 96: told that the police couldn't
Speaker 22: put him there
until
Speaker 22: they had evidence that the timeline had changed. And when the timeline had changed, all of a sudden he was
present at
Speaker 22: the scene of the crime. And
the important part is he
Speaker 1: said he wasn't there. And
if you say you
Speaker 1: weren't at the scene of the crime, but you turned out you were at the scene of the crime, you look guilty. In fact, the jury
Speaker 199: agreed and they convicted him of two counts of murder and he's serving life in prison. He'll never walk free again. Well, this
Speaker 12: one, this...
case
Speaker 12: that I'm making here is that
Speaker 22: we might have a similar situation going on here where somebody who claims they were somewhere
else was actually near
Speaker 22: the scene of the crime.
And then the final one
Speaker 35: today on OJ
Simpson, the
Speaker 35: timeline doesn't make sense.
The timeline just doesn't make
Speaker 199: sense. In
fact, the
Speaker 199: timeline makes perfect sense if someone else did it. Maybe his son
Speaker 199: Jason? I don't know. That's an opinion. I don't know whether Jason did it or not.
But there's a book
Speaker 247: out there that's pretty compelling if you read it. It's pretty compelling that he did it.
Well, I suggest that the timeline
Speaker 248: doesn't make sense for Tyler Robinson.
Too much coming and
Speaker 226: going from campus. Too many changes of clothes.
Too much walking around. Too
Speaker 226: much driving around.
And the kicker for me
Speaker 42: is...
They
Speaker 42: have to know where his car was because he has a modern car. It
Speaker 199: has GPS. They're going to be able to tell where he parked it. They can subpoena all that information. He had a phone in his pocket. We just saw it on the images of him walking up the stairs.
And then we have eyewitness
Speaker 249: testimony that says the
guy
Speaker 111: who actually The...
Speaker 111: Everybody was reporting did it looked a whole lot more like this guy.
And this guy's timeline makes perfect sense. Because we don't
Speaker 88: have any video footage of him driving back and forth from campus. We
don't have any video
Speaker 196 (lower-pitched voice): footage of him changing clothes multiple times, walking through neighborhoods, driving through neighborhoods.
I'm
Speaker 48: curious about all the inconsistencies
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): that we've uncovered just tonight. Not
to mention all
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): the inconsistencies from everything else we've uncovered. Not
to mention
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): all the lies we've caught people telling.
I don't know how Charlie
Speaker 71: died. I
wish I
Speaker 71: did. It'd make it a lot easier.
I don't know
Speaker 71: if he was shot with a weapon. I tend to say no because there's no through and through wound. I
don't know if there's
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): something exploded under his shirt. It sure looks like it. You cannot argue that a gunshot wound to the neck would do what happened under his shirt with his pendant coming up and hitting him in the neck and
the whole
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): shirt rising up at once. That doesn't happen if you get shot in the neck. It just doesn't. You can't create a scenario in the wild where it happens.
I
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): don't know if he was electrocuted. It sure looked like his hands were awfully burned up and damaged, even in
Speaker 96: the creepy images where Erica is, for some reason, releasing video of her touching his hands and crying into the casket. You can actually see on his left
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): hand two wounds
Speaker 96: on his
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): hand. It's not consistent with getting shot in the neck.
I don't know how we explain
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): the two dots.
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): that are on his arm that look like puncture
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): wounds or maybe taser wounds i don't know how we explain that
i don't know how we explain all
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): the weird stuff that
was going
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): on around him dan flood stepping forward
and touching his
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): upper right arm right before the big bang i don't know how we explain that
i don't know how we
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): explain brian harpole being weird and getting caught lying afterwards on sean ryan's show
I
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): don't know how he explained that there was no security plan in place the next day for Charlie Kirk in Colorado. I
don't know how he explained that Brian
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): Harpole had not booked any flights, our opinion, that he'd not booked any flights
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): after the Utah Valley event.
That's not even to get into some of the
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): more speculative things that we don't know. We don't know what happened to the AES plant in rural Tennessee that exploded.
we don't
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): know who was on that Hebrew city flight to Nashville. We don't know what was in Butch Hibbs' front pocket when he showed up. We
don't know why
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): Butch Hibbs was there. We don't
Speaker 96: know why Butch Hibbs hung around for so long afterwards, and every time someone was being interviewed, Butch Hibbs would position
Speaker 133: himself in the background to hear what they were saying. We don't know any of this.
But what we do
Speaker 249: know is you and I have been lied to over and over again by our government,
by our law
Speaker 2: enforcement, by
TPUSA, by Erica
Speaker 2: Kirk, by Andrew Colvitt. I mean,
by now, I think it's a pretty
Speaker 12: established fact, Candace has pretty much established it, that Andrew
Colvitt and
Speaker 12: Erica Kirk
called
Speaker 251: the surgeon on a three-way call.
the surgeon
Speaker 247: basically said that doesn't look like a 30-06 wound. It
would have gone
Speaker 247: through the back of his neck. It might have decapitated him.
And then Erica Kirk put
Speaker 247: the words in his mouth, but what if he was really healthy and had a very strong neck? What
if it was a
Speaker 247: frangible round? Give me something, doc. Any way it could have happened. If
you're
Speaker 1: just trying to get to the truth of why your husband's dead, why are you planting those seeds in the surgeon's ears?
why
Speaker 12: not just let the evidence come to you? Why not just wait and see what the autopsy report shows? We
don't know why
Speaker 13: Mikey McCoy turned and walked away within 800 milliseconds,
Speaker 96: less than nine-tenths of a second after the Big Bang. We don't know why
Terrell
Speaker 97: Farnsworth went and videoed himself strangely and weirdly See
Speaker 47: you
Speaker 92: next
Speaker 63: week.
As
Speaker 97: Charlie Kirk is
Speaker 47: being transported to the getaway vehicle
and he's
Speaker 47: in here taking a selfie,
Speaker 92: Charlie's dead. Charlie's dead. We
don't know why
Speaker 92: he's doing that.
We don't know why
Speaker 63: the sound guy turned and winced
half a second
Speaker 63: before
Speaker 42: the Big Bang. We don't know that.
when I look
Speaker 42: at the image of him doing it, it looks to me as if he knows a big bang is coming and he's bracing because if you've
Speaker 18: been on a gun range, you kind
of die away
Speaker 18: a little bit when you're about to hear a big bang.
This all deeply
Speaker 252: saddens me. Deeply, deeply saddens
Speaker 249: me.
I think
Speaker 249: back to the O.J. case. What if we'd have known about all these facts about Jason Simpson leading
Speaker 253: up
to the
Speaker 253: O.J. Simpson case?
Would we have looked at O.J.
Speaker 111: differently? I mean, if you go into polite society, and I do this because this is the way I am, but
if you go into
Speaker 111: polite
Speaker 249: society and someone raises O.J. Simpson's name and you say, you
know he
Speaker 249: didn't do it, right?
They look
Speaker 249: at you like,
they look at
Speaker 254: you like you're nuts. It's the power
Speaker 252: of propaganda. It's the power of the entire national media repeating over and over and over and over and over for weeks, months, years, a certain
Speaker 19: narrative that they're drilling into your head with billions. If you had to buy the advertising of all those people on television, all those people on radio, that's not what they're doing.
Speaker 19: telling you over and over, if you said, I want to tell everyone OJ
did it and I
Speaker 19: want to put just as
Speaker 13: much emphasis on it as all those broadcasts did, it would cost you literally billions of dollars.
Well, guess
Speaker 13: what? Billions of dollars of advertising works. It just
Speaker 43: works.
You give me that much advertising, I can
Speaker 255: convince you of anything.
I can convince you we live in a simulation. I can
Speaker 193: convince you the world is flat.
I can
Speaker 193: convince you we went to the moon. And that's
why I'm deeply saddened by this. Not
Speaker 9: because, and it saddens me that Tyler Robinson's on trial for his life, but what saddens me the
Speaker 47: most, though, is that hundreds of millions of people are being misled
day in and
Speaker 47: day out.
and that
Speaker 111: there are possibly murderers or people who plotted a murder who
might get
Speaker 111: away with it.
Like the people who
Speaker 111: arranged for the murder of John F. Kennedy, for example,
Speaker 17: or RFK, or MLK, or Malcolm X. These
people all
Speaker 17: got away
with it. Nobody was ever held
Speaker 57: accountable. I mean, Sirhan Sirhan was, but he didn't do it.
Speaker 57: Hinkley was, but he didn't do it.
Lee Harvey Oswald
Speaker 57: was, but he didn't do it.
So what you have is a
Speaker 1: decades-long history
of people
Speaker 1: murdering Americans in an organized, coordinated fashion, walking away with no consequences, no
Speaker 199: earthly consequences.
So
Speaker 199: temporal consequences. I'm convinced there are eternal consequences to that action.
And so, yeah, I
Speaker 58: get sad covering this story. I genuinely do. I take a tremendous interest in it.
It's bigger than
Speaker 58: Charlie Kirk. It's so much bigger than
Speaker 256: Charlie Kirk. It's
so much bigger than Charlie
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): Kirk. We got a lot more for you this week. We're going to have a big week, guys. So stand by if you are...
I'm going
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): to be here with us all week. In all
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): likelihood, I will be back tomorrow. I don't usually do a show on Tuesday, but I probably will just because we've got a lot to talk about. So let me
go through some of
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): these chats. I might have
to do
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): it in a little abbreviated fashion tonight, but I will get to as many as I possibly can. Youngest of 11 can relate to the Coleman's. You
can relate to the
Speaker 66: younger Coleman's for sure.
Speaker 257: Um,
let's see
Speaker 257: here. Um, uh, did I see the email about the car across
Speaker 258: from Phil Lyman's aunt possibly being the same one parked in front of the chicken coop? Uh, I did not, but it's not the same car, two different
Speaker 71: cars. Um, I remember the first week of news and views and thinking, is this station paying these clowns, but you improved and then you became great now. Wow. Go max. Um,
I remember the first week of news and views and thinking, is this station paying these
Do I
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): know you? If I don't know you, News and Views was a radio program I did years ago. The first week was
Speaker 66: terrible. I still have it on audio somewhere. I've gone back and listened to it. It's horrible. I
wondered if
Speaker 66: they were paying these clowns. So thanks for hanging around all these years. That's
a decade and a half
Speaker 66: ago.
uh and
Speaker 258: thanks for the compliment uh would you shout out my husband sean hey sean in the er last night we're home now he's resting would really put a smile on his face what up sean get well soon brother uh be wrong my man i just want to thank you for all you do sent you an email about tr's car from the last episode i could swear to a spotlight and mirror on it challenge your cop cars near uvu keep moving on um i'll
check it
Speaker 258: out
i
Speaker 259: shall check it out uh
hi baron just
Speaker 178: cracked up last night with your baby mama drama rendition always feel good watching your show love you
crisis king
Speaker 178: yeah wolves in finance i cracked up watching him
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): do baby
mama drama uh
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): that was fantastic that was absolutely fantastic stellar if you i do say my uh do say so myself
My
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): heart has been
Speaker 261: hurting for CK and everyone who loves him. Now, my brain after Jesse's series, it's compelling, honestly. The whole incident was followed after has
been
Speaker 12: such a roller coaster. I've been following it. I even watched Jesse's show that he released late this afternoon
while I
Speaker 12: was getting ready for this show.
I don't agree with
Speaker 71: him,
Speaker 262: but I don't fault him for running down the rabbit trail and see. Maybe he'll convince me. But for right now, I do not. I do not.
I
Speaker 262: agree with him.
Speaker 21: Candace Owens, the personal and historical angle. Barron with the analytical and legal angle. And Wolves with the financial and fraud angle. All bases covered. Yes, but we're always looking for more researchers. We're always looking for more shows. So if you find one, let me know. Let me know. Let's see.
Speaker 18: Let's see. Hi, Baron. This is my first super chat, and you're the only membership I've ever bought. Keep going, Max. Love your show. Crisis King. Crisis King indeed, Robin. Welcome to the members channel.
Speaker 18: I may do a quick member show tomorrow. It would have to be quick because I'm going to be getting ready
Speaker 21: for a regular show in all likelihood tomorrow night. I can't promise you, but I'm 80% sure I'll do a show tomorrow afternoon or tomorrow night. Not sure which.
What
Speaker 5: time did the Egyptian plane leave? Where did it go?
The
Speaker 30: plane that's on the tarmac there left on September 13th.
It went
Speaker 30: to Goose Bay, Canada, and then overseas.
Speaker 263: Okay.
so
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): that answers your question there uh chally picked from x asked
Speaker 130: hubs oh had two chargers and a challenger he spotted a b pillar and a handle to the left of the pole four door we love you
Speaker 2: and wolves and finance baby mama drama yeah i have ruled out every car i've put up so far but i i've only ruled it out because
i get good feedback like that
Speaker 2: but i have put a number of cars up
Speaker 38: on x let me just tell you
where i
Speaker 38: am on that i've looked at every car i can find
From
Speaker 38: that day, because I have
Speaker 12: satellite imagery from that day or high aerial imagery from that day. I cannot find Tyler's car anywhere.
Not anywhere
Speaker 12: it's supposed to be. And that's disturbing because
his car
Speaker 261: should be there. I
was angry after
Speaker 261: watching Jesse on fire series about CK faking his death. It hurts that Charlie's gone, but that's not it.
Jesse's theory leaves so
Speaker 261: many questions unanswered. Keep digging everyone. Yeah, I'm willing to continue listening to his channel.
And I
Speaker 261: like Jesse. As far as just being a talented broadcaster, the guy is stellar. I mean, he's just a really good broadcaster.
And
Speaker 12: so I always am willing to listen to someone who's just a great broadcaster. Going back to the subject of AK having EK
Speaker 17: phone, if this is true, then the amazing Mikey McCoy could not have called EK as claimed.
Christ is
Speaker 17: king. Well, that would explain the short
Speaker 111: phone call, wouldn't it?
that
Speaker 111: would explain the very short phone call. And it
Speaker 247: would explain why he's not released the records. He just gave a written timeline. Or
maybe he did release
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): the records, but I have not seen them. I'll be happy to look at them. Absolutely happy to
look at them. From the
Speaker 35: Grumblers, just testing this, I've never donated to Rumble. Approved, received. Sent you an email
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): on OJ, dated 124, family connection to DA's office. Happy
to look
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): at it.
Happy to look at
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): it.
uh
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): zodiac signs be damned
Speaker 71: which hoodie was baron
Speaker 42: wearing the first time you watched i am a bean paste atarius what's the supposed tpusa ek motive for
Speaker 12: lying about the flights thanks baron i put a lot of thought into this that's a great question i put
a lot of thought into
Speaker 12: this
a couple of
Speaker 12: things I've come up with. One is she did not want to have to fake a
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): reaction on the ground in Arizona. Far easier to just go ahead and be in Utah. Second, if something goes wrong, she's on the ground in Utah. Third, if it's a team thing, there's
Speaker 12: always a quarterback. There's a leader. There's somebody who's able to pull the no sign at the last second. And
I wonder if that
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): was her. And if you've got to have that person I don't
know.
They
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): got to be on the ground in front of everybody. You can't risk a communication lapse. Fourth, you know how the president, when there is a giant operation going on,
sits in
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): the
Speaker 3: situation room and they've got all the screens pulled up and he can see all the helmet cams from the different soldiers and all? You know how that works?
Well, she can't have a
Speaker 265: situation room in Scottsdale. Someone would be watching it. They'd say, what the hell are you doing?
Get on the ground in
Speaker 199: Utah, you can get you a situation room.
So I
Speaker 199: think there are lots of motivations for being on the ground.
I think there are
Speaker 199: lots of them. Thank you for asking this great question. Had confession last Saturday after 40 years, had communion, life transforming, two days, no
Speaker 193: wine, reading Rome Sweet Home. Thanks. You sound like you're heading in the right direction.
Getting
Speaker 111: sober, going back to church, reading spiritual books. This is great. Thank you for sharing. How
does a
Speaker 111: homeschool mama
Speaker 193: get a gift
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): membership? I don't know. The gift memberships, I think, are randomly given out.
I think
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): they're just randomly giving out. I'm not sure. Congratulations on homeschooling, though. We've done
it
Speaker 71: with our kids, and it's amazing. Have
you done
Speaker 71: a deep dive into the super sus? Stacey Sheridan. It's
Speaker 122: coming. The research is already being done. Frank Turek. Same. Terrell Farnsworth. Same. Ryan Harpole. Sort of. And Jack Posobiec. Major
Speaker 71: clues likely. I'm not sure what Jack Posobiec deep dive would give. I mean, I know a lot, but I'm not sure what that would give.
but
Speaker 71: the
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): rest are on their way. Stand by,
Speaker 261: stand by. Hi, been watching you since the Google searched Tyler Robinson and haven't
missed
Speaker 5: since. That was the first Tyler Robinson. That's episode one of this series that if you go back and look at them, this is, I think, 65. So you've been around.
Beginning to lose
Speaker 5: faith in
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): the system, but at least you're restoring faith in some people and our creator.
Who loves
Speaker 199: us? Yes, our creator loves us.
Speaker 199: Crater absolutely loves this.
Why is
Speaker 199: this one blue? That's fancy. Frank
Speaker 71: Turk says EK arrived at the hospital about three hours after he was shot. And another time he said she arrived at the hospital around 4 p.m.
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah. I mean, I think that's consistent. She wouldn't arrive before her plane landed. Right. So three hours after would be 3.23, which, you know, in the heat of battle
Speaker 89: might be considered around four.
Speaker 266: So, yeah.
trying
Speaker 71: to i gotta be a little selective tonight because we're already at two hours and
Speaker 12: there's there's quite a few so and just take heart i do read every super chat after the show while i'm sitting here i do the editing and while it's processing i go
back and
Speaker 12: read every super chat so everything you guys say to me
in the supers i
Speaker 247: get i absolutely get it um
even if
Speaker 247: i can't pull it up and respond to it i do get it uh will you ask ian to upload hillary clinton and john
Speaker 71: Podesta to the web.
Speaker 71: So my understanding of how the web is going to be is once he finishes the build out, this is kind of like a beta test with the Einstein files. Once he builds it out, though, we'll get access to the code in a way where we can upload
Speaker 64: our own data. That's my understanding. I'll ask him if I'm right on that, but that's my understanding. I hope that's my understanding. I hope that's correct.
But if that's right,
Speaker 64: we can upload
Speaker 71: lots of stuff into the web.
Speaker 71: It's a great program. If you're not playing with it, it's a great program. Episode 285 at 253, Candace Owen said that on the eve of September 10, Tyler was three hours away in Panguitch, Utah, at a place called Cowboy Steakhouse,
and his
Speaker 71: grandma lives there as well. Can
you find his
Speaker 71: track, his car backwards, and see where he traveled from? I can't. So here's the program I'm using as a single static image from that day, or actually it's two.
Two
Speaker 71: static images from that day, slightly different times.
And so if your
Speaker 71: car
Speaker 62: wasn't visible, and it looks to me to be like one of them maybe around 11, one about
Speaker 65: 1130, if your car wasn't visible in that hour
or so
Speaker 65: leading up to the program starting, it's not going to be there.
So I can't go to
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): the steakhouse and look later,
and I
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): can't follow him down the interstate. That's not the
way
Speaker 71: satellite images work. And frankly,
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): we're glad because that would be the creepiest program
of all
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): time, and none of us would be safe.
you
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): would all be subject to being spied on at all times. Can you
Speaker 64: imagine you had a creepy ex who stalked you a little bit and they had that access? They could just watch you in real time wherever you went?
That's terrifying. That's
Speaker 268: terrible. Or maybe you're the creepy ex.
Speaker 267: Maybe you're
Speaker 269: like, dang it.
I'm so
Speaker 269: close. I
Speaker 42: thought I had it. Has anyone done a deep dive into Y refi? I have not. Millions in student loans, set up caps on table.
Speaker 42: Helped carry him to the
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): SUV. Charlie said college is a scam. They had to despise that.
I don't
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): think
Speaker 8: that would have made him murder him. I mean, Charlie said college is a scam and then spent his entire career going on college campuses.
So, OJ's son
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): was the murderer IMO. Just want to say it first. Yeah, I got there. What time did you say that? 641? Yeah, you said it before I did.
How about I didn't get there to like
Speaker 270: 645 or 650?
Good call. And
Speaker 270: again,
Speaker 153: just my opinion. They're in the EKASU Spring 2020 grad program. The fall one shows where Tyler Boyer on the last page where
Speaker 154: they show noted Board of Regents members.
I have to look at
Speaker 271: that. I cannot find the spring one.
I cannot find
Speaker 132 (lower-pitched voice): the spring one. If someone has a copy of the spring 2012 graduate program, commencement
Speaker 38: ceremony program from ASU, I want to see it. I've been looking for it. I cannot find it. I've
put out
Speaker 38: a lot of feelers and have not gotten anything back. What
do you make of
Speaker 38: Alex Jones attacking Candace Owens? What do you think is his motive or who is behind it? I don't know. I don't know. I try to stay out of other people's spats if I can. Um...
And
Speaker 38: sometimes I get dragged into them. You
guys saw
Speaker 38: that here recently. Two other creators
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): fighting, and I get dragged into the middle of it. It's miserable. I don't
want to
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): get in the middle of it, and I don't want to speculate. You
could probably
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): guess what
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): I think, but I don't want to speculate. I
had to run and put
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): on my bean paste hoodie
Speaker 247: to watch my favorite high IQ podcast. God bless you and your family. Well, God bless you and your bean paste hoodie.
Speaker 272: I'll
see you next time.
AK
Speaker 13: pattern of exposing EK steel neck for H
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): pick alibi hug on tarmac just enough for us to figure out that it's false without appearing sus to TPSA still rooting for him to be the mole. If
Andrew
Speaker 273: Colvitt is the mole. It's
the wildest mole in the
Speaker 273: history
Speaker 5: of mankind. Because he comes off as not a mole. He comes off as a mole.
it's
Speaker 5: kind of a low IQ bumbling
Speaker 274: idiot who keeps accidentally revealing things he's not supposed to speaking out of school.
I've been thinking
Speaker 247: about Cabot Phillips gender reveal for balloons and a dozen cupcakes would be the lame lamest gender reveal party ever. And that's saying something that's, that's assuming they're not all the lamest gender reveal parties of all time. I'm glad that wasn't a thing when we were having kids, maybe on the
last
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): couple, it had sort of become a thing, but
yeah.
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): certainly not in the first one. I remember hearing about it the first time. I thought, whoa,
Speaker 247: whoa, you're going to go to someone's house just to find out what kind of baby they're having. Oh yeah. We got to
take a
Speaker 247: gift. You have to take a gift to find out what kind of baby they're having. Yeah. And they're going to shoot off fireworks and it's either going
to be
Speaker 247: pink or blue.
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): What? I mean, my brain could not comprehend it. Now, maybe it's a thing and you guys love it. I'm not making fun of you. I'm just saying
it was
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): totally not a thing. And when
I first
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): heard about it, it seemed very bizarre.
Speaker 127: confirmed. You have a lower half when you
were on
Speaker 127: Candice's show. I have legs.
Speaker 275: I have legs. I
love your
Speaker 12: show. I watch everyone I can. Thank you for relentlessly searching for the truth, praying for
Speaker 1: y'all's safety. Pizza update. So the pizza has not been back, but yes, I have legs. Oh, also, I squatted today. Yeah,
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): squatted. We did a seven-by-one back squat and
uh,
No
Speaker 21: PR, but it felt pretty heavy under there. And so I had to use my legs. I had to use my legs. Yeah,
I've not
Speaker 21: seen the Chinook back since then. So hopefully it's gone. I found your glass redneck stemware on Etsy. If anyone's looking. If
anyone's
Speaker 78: looking. Apparently I made $4.99 tonight I didn't know about. I promise. You promised me $4.99 for wearing that hoodie color. Pink slime. Okay, thanks guys.
I'm
Speaker 18: doing what I can, guys, doing all I can out here,
Speaker 96: doing all I can. Remember, Rob's covered with blood sermon. Rob said he has another son, Justin, who also works there, but that isn't Strife, right? No, it's
not
Speaker 71: Justin Strife. Why
do we never
Speaker 71: hear about Rob's other son? Why is his last name different from McCoy? I don't know,
and I'm
Speaker 71: not 100% keyed in on that. I know he has at least
Speaker 262: one adopted child, maybe two, and maybe that's what
he's talking about, but I
Speaker 262: don't know.
There's so
Speaker 276: much weirdness at
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): TPUSA. There's something weird with the Russians in TPUSA, and I can't figure out what it is. But,
like, Tyler
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): Boyer speaks Russian. Elizabeth McCoy speaks Russian. One
of Rob
Speaker 197 (lower-pitched voice): McCoy's kids is Russian. There's some Russian weirdness going on at the top of TPUSA, and I can't
figure it out. I can't
Speaker 5: figure it out. How do we get admin
to
Speaker 42: answer why FBI is standing down? So many unanswered questions, presses...
Speaker 13: A-W-F-Ultimundus, J.D. needs to answer to what, why, Mikey McCoy phone call immediately after, bless your family, Christ is king, Christ is king indeed. Yeah, that's probably
Speaker 96: one of the weirdest facts of the entire thing is Charlie Kirk goes down and Mikey McCoy picks up the phone and
calls the vice
Speaker 277: president of the United States.
Mikey McCoy is
Speaker 277: 22 at this time.
and
Speaker 278: the vice president answers. Come
Speaker 279: on. Stop it. Stop
Speaker 71: it. That's ludicrous. I refuse to believe it. I refuse to believe it. G'day from
Speaker 261: New Zealand. Are you related? Have you heard of Dr. John B. Coleman? I have not, and I am not related. I know
a John Coleman, but
Speaker 261: not that one.
I
Speaker 261: saw a talk he gave about the Committee of 300 who ruled the world in the 90s. Pretty scary stuff. Also, ever go to the TLM, Crisis King? God bless. I do
go to
Speaker 261: the TLM quite often.
Yeah, I
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): do. I'm
not going to tell
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): you which one.
Speaker 223: Don't need that. But yeah, I go quite often.
Hey,
Speaker 223: Johnny, two times, I told you a few shows ago
that I
Speaker 223: was at Nipplegate, I remember that, and hung out with Kato, I remember
Speaker 280: that, thought about that tonight. He said OJ for sure did it, also that OJ was advised to stop taking arthritis meds and his hands swole up.
Speaker 281: Now, you
expect me to
Speaker 242: believe Kato Kaelin who became a reality TV star?
Speaker 5: I'm sorry. Absolutely not. He doesn't have a clue. He doesn't have a clue.
But
Speaker 5: thank you for sharing your story. Your brush with greatness.
The
Speaker 247: great Tato Kaelin. Mikey McCoy could only be so happy to be
Speaker 38: called the great Mikey McCoy. Brandy and Billy, the
Speaker 64: first time I watched them, younger one had to go. She announced, I have to go pee. I'll be right back. Crack me up. Other one filled in until she got back.
Speaker 223: Take your break. We will too. I
don't need
Speaker 223: it yet, but we're
getting
Speaker 282: there.
we're
Speaker 88: getting there you know i used to be able to like down the big the maybe it's the maybe it's the blackberry stuff these are
Speaker 199: great sodas by the way they only have 30 calories uh it's a kombucha and
it has no fake
Speaker 199: sweetener either just very lightly
Speaker 71: sweetened delicious uh mrs coleman's been picking them up by the dozen great
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): opening you
are the best hard
Speaker 71: to argue
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): with you
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): uh i remember all of this also your opening for jackie was awesome as well oh thank you that's very kind of you
that one
Speaker 24: was fun to write the jackie one was fun
uh my mother
Speaker 24: sat in front of
the tv
Speaker 24: and sobbed when they were chasing oj and the white bronco i was a child didn't understand but thought it was very
Speaker 261: weird so i
Speaker 24: was at a friend's house i think we were
Speaker 261: there to watch um i remember his name and i'm not gonna say it was just up the road here not far away from where
I know we
Speaker 261: had
Speaker 284: pizza. I think we were there for an NBA finals game. Maybe we were watching. I can't remember why we were gathered at his house, but there were like eight or 10 of us. Maybe it was
a birthday party
Speaker 261: or something.
Speaker 284: But I want
to
Speaker 261: say there was
Speaker 12: a basketball game one. And then the basketball game got interrupted to watch OJ. And boy, we were glued. You guys, you guys who were that young cannot possibly understand how big of a star OJ Simpson was. He was huge, a huge star. I can't think of anybody today
who is
Speaker 12: equivalent to what O.J. Simpson was. Because you would have to be one of the all-time greats at your sport,
very
Speaker 96: well-known, famous for that, then flip over and be like a pretty well-known actor in some pretty highly viewed movies, and then flip over and be like a pretty influential and well-known sports broadcaster on Monday Night Football, when Monday
Night
Speaker 12: Football was like the biggest thing on TV. It's
just that there's
Speaker 12: nothing like him. Nothing like O.J. It was so huge watching him drive down the road.
Speaker 12: Uh, watch
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): documentary, my brother, the serial killer. There's a guy named Glenn Rogers, who I think is a viable suspect in the OJ case. Very compelling evidence in it.
Never heard that. Thank you. Uh, everyone since
Speaker 17: high school, when the OJ trial happened has called me crazy, including my husband, because I said, OJ didn't do it. His son did. I knew I wasn't crazy.
You're not
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): crazy, ma'am.
Thank you for the
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): vindication. I hope you're listening. I hope so too.
They very
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): well could be.
Speaker 71: this is interesting you guys keep bringing up Jesse on fire so I'm going to I'm not going to pull up every comment that mentions it but I
Speaker 24: will pull up this one to respond to it Jesse on fire's theory provocative but Candace Owens 270 said she accepted
Charlie
Speaker 32: Kirk death after trusted friend saw his body and
confirm you
Speaker 287: are a
better be a
Speaker 287: good emoji
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): I can't
see it
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): from here I better be something awesome I
better not be
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): like a middle finger or something
Speaker 282: um We'll be
Speaker 89: right
Speaker 24: back.
I
Speaker 282: think he's dead. I
think he's
Speaker 282: dead. It's a little weird that they won't tell us where he's buried, but
I think he's
Speaker 282: dead. I think he's
Speaker 89: dead. Ah, your opening statement was fire. I read Deer's book last year and was shocked that I'd never heard it on any mainstream media
Speaker 24: source because of how compelling it was. Changed my view, 180 degrees on the OJ case. Same.
But
Speaker 24: same, it's absolutely compelling. If you've never read William Deere's book, it's
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): worth the read. If a widow is removed
from a
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): will a month before
Speaker 24: a murder, isn't the widow a suspect in the eyes of the law? Is that true? Is that the fact here? I've not heard that. And
what if the
Speaker 24: letter is proven to be forged
Speaker 288: that caused to change her?
to
Speaker 288: charge her. Is that cause to charge her? I don't
Speaker 289: know what letter you're talking about. I haven't heard that she was removed from the will.
Speaker 71: You're bringing facts to the table that I'm just unfamiliar with. If you want to email me those facts, that's fine. And
I had an
Speaker 71: email. I'm
not even going
Speaker 71: to comment on it.
I had an
Speaker 129: email today that definitively stated, if you watch this video, this question will be answered. And I normally don't do that, but it was a short video and I was like, fine, he said it definitively would answer it. I wanted to
Speaker 247: know the answer to the question. I
watched
Speaker 43: the video twice and
I wanted
Speaker 43: to say, I wanted to write back and be like, did you watch the video? Like, you know
Speaker 23: it didn't answer the question, right? It didn't even address it. Like, it did not even address the
Speaker 290: question, much less answer it.
I
Speaker 290: thought maybe he sent me the
Speaker 291: wrong link. I don't know. Short video said I'm too big of a too big of a
wasn't too
Speaker 223: big of a distraction. If it, if it was OJ, if it was Jason, why is OJ considering unaliving himself on his way to Mexico
Speaker 24: and the white Bronco driven by his friend Al Cowlings with 8,000, not all conspiracy theories are true. That's compelling. I mean, I'm not saying it's a hundred percent. I am convinced it was Jason. The answer is,
as long as
Speaker 24: they thought it was OJ and he was on the run, Jason was safe. You don't, maybe you don't have kids, but
I would protect my kids
Speaker 24: at all costs. I
don't care what
Speaker 24: they did. I
would protect my
Speaker 24: kids at all costs. My kid cannot make a mistake that I would not help my kid on. They just can't.
I'm not saying
Speaker 24: I would take active steps to, to
thwart law
Speaker 24: enforcement. I don't, you know, but if, if law enforcement had keyed in on me and all I had to do was flee,
If
Speaker 24: my kid is safe,
I might get
Speaker 24: overseas
Speaker 38: and figure out what to do next.
I don't know. I would never let
Speaker 38: my kid be hurt.
I would never let my kid
Speaker 38: be hurt.
John 832 has been
Speaker 292: my way of life since I became a father. First Super Chat. Joined members for the first time ever on YouTube
Speaker 31: community. Love from Chile. Go, Max. Want to seek confession but
afraid
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): because...
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): something I don't know what you're saying there I'm only reading this because
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): I get a chance to use my new Bible
oh I'm in
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): the wrong John I'm in the first letter to John not the gospel of John John 832
you
Speaker 262: say and you'll know the truth and the truth will make you well that's pretty good
That's a
Speaker 293: good thing to live by. Yeah, I remember where I was when the verdict was read, too. I was in high school.
Everybody was just
Speaker 130: aghast. Everybody was aghast. I'm in Santa Barbara. We'll do any detective work you need. I
might have to get in touch with
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): you. I
can't think of any
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): off the top of my head, but...
I
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): might need to get in touch with you.
Speaker 118 (lower-pitched voice): Let's see. I'm trying not to be duplicative since we have so many. So if they're basically asking or saying the same thing, I'm sort
of being
Speaker 118 (lower-pitched voice): selective.
Speaker 26: Barron, just like Ellen's girlfriend. Barron. Oh, my gosh. So
what
Speaker 133: this, yes. What this person is referring to is Ellen's girlfriend got in a wreck.
and they
Speaker 133: said
Speaker 88: she died. They had her in a body bag or something. She was in a white bag that was zipped up. She unzips it and starts trying
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): to climb out, and they push her back into the bag and shove her in the ambulance, and then she supposedly dies at the hospital. If
you haven't seen the
Speaker 126: video, it's wild. And
I thought the same
Speaker 126: thing when they said, oh,
Speaker 119: we got a guy hanging out the car. You do?
You do
Speaker 119: have a guy
Speaker 294: hanging out the car.
Would there be traffic cameras
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): that document a car driving with a person hanging out of it? First to your first question. No, the dispatcher did not say he was in an ambulance,
said the
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): ambulance was on the way.
Obviously, he didn't get
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): the ambulance. I don't know if there
would be
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): traffic cameras documenting it or not. That's interesting.
Speaker 295: That'd be an interesting question.
That'd be
Speaker 13: interesting. This is a good question. Somebody outside of TPUSA leadership, but
Speaker 71: within TPUSA knows everything as well. Think of it as the equivalent of a human, of them being cute. Character
in
Speaker 173: James Bond, they cannot, will not say anything ever. Well, can you blame them?
But I can assure
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): you people inside of TPUSA are still talking. As
I talk
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): to them.
How do you think I know
Speaker 104 (lower-pitched voice): about the flights?
how do
Speaker 296: you think I know about a
Speaker 247: lot of the stuff we talk about
they still
Speaker 247: talking what about the picture you saw of his neck it was his chest so I'm not
Speaker 3: sure what we're what we're asking there
yes what
Speaker 3: if Charlie was
Speaker 146 (higher-pitched voice): trying to get away from him that's what I thought you guys are keen the high IQ outfit Joe
the high
Speaker 130: IQ outfit
As a
Speaker 130: fellow Catholic convert, I'm so grateful for your
Speaker 71: perspective and earnest pursuit of truth. I would love to hear your perspective on the Gilgamesh in Iran story someday. God bless. Any particular aspect of it, that's a big question.
A lot of
Speaker 71: Gilgamesh in Iran story
Speaker 274: to cover. I'm
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): not sure which one you're talking about.
Speaker 211: So the
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): way his neck slammed down behind the table, couldn't that break his neck? It was really hard hit and kind of bounced. I don't think so. Not
like six or
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): seven vertebrae, particularly not the C1 and 2. That's up there. That's hard to break without really trying. So
I don't think they
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): would have done it.
I don't
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): think they would have done
it.
Speaker 261: uh but baron twist my arm already joining the membership fund go max check the email allegedly jesus christ is king indeed uh i'll check
it is
Speaker 130: there dash cam footage
Speaker 87: of the yeah
maybe you know they said that a
Speaker 87: police car caught up with them maybe there's dash caravan footage hadn't thought about that someone put in
a
Speaker 261: foyer request for the dash cam footage please although they'll probably say it's part of the investigation and deny it but you can at least ask. And if they get...
Speaker 71: 26,611 of them, then they'll know that they need to have a good reason why they're not going to release it. Please explain why all the timestamps start with 14. I don't know what that means. I
would love to help
Speaker 71: you with that, but that's very vague
Speaker 253: and I'm sorry, I can't answer
Speaker 48: it. Is there any way to pull up the aerial satellite footage right after the event? No, I have two static images, both before the event.
That's all
Speaker 48: I have.
Speaker 48: I
Speaker 71: don't know any other way to explain that. That's not how satellite works.
Like when
Speaker 71: Google comes
Speaker 3: over and does an image
of your home, it
Speaker 3: does it like once every year or two. We just happened to hit the jackpot and get one right before the event started.
Would I work for the defense team if
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): Erica sues
Speaker 298: Candace? Which defense team? Tyler Robinson's or Candace's?
Speaker 298: Candace can hire good lawyers She has good lawyers I've read
the pleadings She's
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): got fine lawyers Fine lawyers She's
good Let's see
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): here The cop requested another unit when he said I need another, I'm a cop as well Oh,
thank
Speaker 299: you
Speaker 2: That's good context, sir Thank you Did everyone who carried him get in the SUV?
No Thank you.
No, I think two of
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): the people did not, if I'm not mistaken. CS
building
Speaker 300: had a line of sight
in the
Speaker 300: 3D model.
Speaker 192: Well, that's good Intel
Speaker 293: trigger. Are you serious? I'll
have to get
Speaker 293: with you offline and we'll have to look at that because that's interesting.
Speaker 293: i've always wondered i thought somebody would
Speaker 261: have been there serving as a lookout because it is the highest place and you have i've gotten on google maps and pulled it down i couldn't tell if it had a direct line of sight um
but i
Speaker 261: thought what a great place to station a lookout because you
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): get a look at every single rooftop and
you would
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): know if somebody's looking at anything going on around
there uh
Speaker 302: that's interesting it's interesting um
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): so this is interesting what if it wasn't Charlie hanging
out of
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): the car but someone in the car who wasn't in on it and
Speaker 3: saw them finish Charlie Kirk off thank you for all you do, Crisis King well
that person should
Speaker 3: have spoken up by now we'd love to hear from him
Speaker 303: we'd
Speaker 31: love to hear from him by the way yeah yeah
is
Speaker 31: saying the
Speaker 3: EK crying next to the casket is trending and getting backlash. And
it says Tyler
Speaker 13: Robinson committed self-deletion the day of the Big Bang. I tagged you.
What is saying
Speaker 13: that? I don't know what you're talking about. I'll look. Are
Speaker 71: you tagged me? If you tag me, I'll never see it.
I don't check social
Speaker 71: media enough to find that. You'll have to email it to me. RealBaronPodcastGmail.com. Barron, another
Speaker 1: banger. Thank you. Joining High IQ Outfit had me thinking deep earlier.
Speaker 1: Pam's D-O-W outburst is very
Speaker 7: sinister. Moral choice to all who hurt it, 401k gains versus crash
and punish the
Speaker 7: wicked. Christ knows our choice.
Christ is
Speaker 13: king. Christ is king indeed. Let me look at the Dow Jones real quickly, ladies and gentlemen, because we're only allowed to worry. Oh, oh, Pam, I got bad news,
Speaker 100: Madam Bondi.
The Dow Jones is
Speaker 100: under 50,000.
Speaker 75: once it crosses 50, we're cooked. Once
it crosses
Speaker 75: 50, we're not allowed
to ask
Speaker 75: any questions. So, Pam, it's below 50. We're
back on
Speaker 75: the table. We're asking about the questions. We're asking all the questions now because
Speaker 304: apparently the 50,000 is the threshold at which you are no longer permitted to ask questions. And
here we
Speaker 304: are asking questions.
Speaker 306: this
Speaker 308: is interesting
Speaker 21: watch someone who was previously
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): working on the roof like innocent as heck like hey they found my screwdriver I've been looking for that
Speaker 309: laughing
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): no no no that screwdriver was planted among the evidence
Speaker 262: ladies and gentlemen in my opinion in
my opinion that
Speaker 262: that was uh that was planted has anyone found out whether there was a shot spotter gun detection technology in the area i don't think utah needs shot spotter there's no
crime you ever look at the
Speaker 310: crime statistics in utah it's
laughable i
Speaker 310: don't even know why they have Please.
I
Speaker 17: mean, it's laughable. I looked it up after the Charlie Kirk death. I thought, well, is Utah like a rough and tumble place? No, it's not. Nobody commits crime. A little domestic violence here and there. A couple batteries,
maybe a
Speaker 17: cornerstone robbery. But
it's not
Speaker 17: like most cities. It's not like most states. I don't
know what they
Speaker 100: talk
Speaker 42: about in the news. Because if you watch the local news anywhere I've ever lived, they just talk about the six murders from that day. What
do they
Speaker 42: talk about in Utah?
Snow is
Speaker 42: melting on the mountains today.
There's
Speaker 311: still salt on the ground near Salt Lake.
There's speed
Speaker 311: testing at the flats. I
mean,
Speaker 69: what do you guys talk about on the news? Because
all we talk
Speaker 17: about is violence, ladies and gentlemen. If you live in Utah, you don't know what it's like. You don't know what it's like.
Speaker 13: 9-9-25, day before the Big Bang, Gaza peace talks sabotaged by a missile strike
by
Speaker 24: our greatest ally inside of Qatar capital.
10-10,
Speaker 261: 2025, precisely one month after Charlie Kirk bang, Hegseth announces 300 Qatari Air Force in Idaho.
Interesting facts to add
Speaker 58: to the timeline.
Speaker 47: Uh, using the OJ case as an example, is there any way justice could be found for Charlie through civil litigation with the person group C suing
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): need to be related to Charlie?
Well, you'd
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): have to have standing. I mean, that's kind of the threshold into any lawsuit. Do
you
Speaker 247: have standing to bring the lawsuit?
Your humble host
Speaker 247: would not, I don't know what your relationship is, but I mean, what would your cause of action be?
If it's a
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): wrongful death cause of action, you, you standing would, you'd have to be the wife or
maybe
Speaker 312: the parents.
i would
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): say the answer is probably no
i would say
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): the answer is probably no you
Speaker 129: might be able to have some sort of equivalent of a derivative claim if
you're a donor maybe
Speaker 129: the tp usa uh do we know if they normally hold
Speaker 261: an ambulance and medics closer to charlie at previous college campus events we need a hole please mug baron my husband says that all the time
Speaker 173: too we're working on it
we're working on it
Speaker 173: uh the merch is coming oh i've got a big announcement
And for
Speaker 173: those of you who love Apple podcast, there's no video, so it's all audio, but we are up and running on Apple. All past episodes are uploaded. Today's episode will
be uploaded
Speaker 173: in the morning. Just like we do with Spotify, we upload it the next morning. So if you're an Apple podcaster, welcome to the family. Welcome to the family. It may be a little
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): difficult to find because until this is the dirty little secret of the way these are, even if they
only pay
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): you pennies,
and
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): they really only pay you pennies a lot of these podcast services um
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): they still will not push you out for distribution until you get monetized i'm clearly not monetized we just got all the stuff up today once they're making their ad revenue then
they
Speaker 12: have all the incentive in the world to make sure people hear your show and listen
to it but
Speaker 12: prior to that it's like you know you know fighting through the jungle
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): to find the show so you can search for
it i
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): hope you find it If you do, five stars. Go ahead and follow along.
But
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): we'll be up there from now on every morning after the show. The new episode will upload just like it
Speaker 313 (lower-pitched voice): does to Spotify, usually by 9 a.m. Sometimes as early as 6 or 7 a.m., but usually by 9 a.m.
If you
Speaker 314: cut Lance's hair, he would
look
Speaker 289: like Tyler.
Yeah, a little bit. Out for birthday
Speaker 5: dinner with the Mrs. Ham.
Speaker 5: She's very concerned you quit your day job. Please tell her it's okay. Thank you. We'll watch
Speaker 247: the show tonight. Pam, just
like and subscribe. Click notifications. Share
Speaker 247: with
Speaker 261: your friends and family.
Watch a few episodes. That's
Speaker 261: how you can assure that I'll be fine.
I'll be
Speaker 35: fine if you're fine. Like, if you'll participate, we'll be fine. Your husband, Matt, here is doing yeoman's work, making sure
Speaker 3: the family's taken care of.
Speaker 3: Uh, so thank you. Thank you. Yes. It was a leap of faith. It was a step out of faith, but
it was taking so
Speaker 3: much of my time to put these shows together. Uh, I
was
Speaker 261: basically working two full-time jobs and I couldn't do it. I couldn't justify it anymore. So I had to give one up and I didn't want to give
the show up.
Speaker 261: So I stuck here and we'll see what happens. Let's hope it works out. Uh, thank you for all your tireless work. How do you
Speaker 38: do it
and not
Speaker 38: get mad about what you find having been an
Speaker 315: attorney? Um, yeah.
I get
Speaker 315: mad. I get sad more than mad.
Speaker 315: sad. You're good, Baron. Too good
at muddying the
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): water. But that's what a good defense attorney does.
Just trying to figure
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): out who did it. I'm not trying to muddy the water.
I'm just trying
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): to
Speaker 173: figure it out. Like we all are. Like we all
Speaker 38: are. Question, why Utah? Why not playing this anywhere else? Well, I don't know. I
mean, you got to do it somewhere. Yeah.
I have
Speaker 206: screenshot from news broadcast and saved news clip of person matching that description in reflection of window. Then looks like military takes them away. Please
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): real baron podcast at gmail.com real baron podcast at gmail.com. I'd love to take a
look at it.
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): Hmm.
Speaker 87: This
is a
Speaker 87: good one. Do any of the guys from that map,
fit
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): that description. I can't see their hair, but they are all three dressed in all black. So in that respect, yes, this is the best I can tell about 30 minutes before I'll pull it up and show you what he's talking
about.
Speaker 280: This is from what I can tell about 30
Speaker 24: minutes, maybe 45 minutes
before the
Speaker 24: big bang. So let's pull that up and I'll show you if
I can take a second
Speaker 24: for the map to load
but let me oh
I can tell
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): where I left off the last time I was looking. I was up near the cemetery in the Dairy Queen. Let me get down here near the
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): campus.
Where was
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): it? Oh, here it is.
And up on
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): 800, which is right here. And
we'll
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): find our three people walking right here. So here's what he's talking about. And I'll zoom
in on
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): it so you can see him. Good memory, sir. Good
Speaker 319 (lower-pitched voice): memory.
Speaker 319 (lower-pitched voice): Um, there
are three
Speaker 319 (lower-pitched voice): people here about 30 minutes or so, maybe 45 minutes before the big bang. They're all dressed head to toe in black.
One of them's wearing
Speaker 319 (lower-pitched voice): a white hat. This guy looks like he's wearing a black hat.
Uh, and this person
Speaker 319 (lower-pitched voice): may
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): have, may not be wearing a hat. I'm not sure.
They may even be wearing
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): gray jeans or blue jeans, but, um, I don't know who these people are.
Speaker 13: This is the route.
Speaker 13: tyler robinson allegedly took in this right here on the left is the house where phil lyman was that had the ring doorbell camera footage where the police
Speaker 320: came to
the door so
Speaker 320: that's what he's talking about i
don't know if that's
Speaker 320: them or not i don't know um i
don't know if
Speaker 320: that was
Speaker 38: them or
And
Speaker 38: Charlie fighting off the people in the SUV nearly broke me. I can't even imagine that. I didn't mean to paint that
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): picture. I just
that you
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): listen to what they said, and I'm giving you my opinion of what it sounded like to me.
I can't even
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): imagine that. And in
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): all of this world, nobody got a picture of a black SUV racing down the highway with someone hanging out of it.
Speaker 321: Yeah.
Yeah.
Speaker 1: using the police scanner evidence is key. Great work, Baron. Where
Speaker 47: is it? Where is the photo? I want to give a huge round of applause to Daisy, who did absolute
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): tremendous work helping gather all this footage or all this audio and put it
together in
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): a format. She's becoming an integral part of the program. Everybody needs support, and she is tremendous support. So...
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): Shout out to her for helping.
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): This show could not have happened today without her. Absolutely.
End of story. No
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): question. So great work by Daisy as well. So where's the photo? Great question.
Great
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): question. They had a photo and a video of this guy. Where is it?
Because my guess
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): is it's not Tyler Robbins.
The photo of Tyler
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): in the
Speaker 93: stairwell, Lance in Tyler's clothes. So family friends recognize him as Tyler.
The
Speaker 93: photo of Lance outside the house looks like the guy in the stairwell, maybe allegedly perhaps, except the hair's all wrong. Unless his hair's tucked up under the hat, maybe. I don't know.
Other than that, the
Speaker 93: hair's all wrong.
I don't
Speaker 93: think the photo, the two Daily Mail photos look anything like that photo showed of Lance with a cat hood and
Speaker 313 (lower-pitched voice): face, nothing like the other two photos. People change. I mean, who knows when that picture was taken? That picture may be five years old.
What he looks
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): like to me is a guy growing and...
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): getting older. I mean, he's now in his early 20s. He might have been
Speaker 322: 16 in that picture. 15, 14, we don't know.
Lovey
Speaker 5: shows if the no burial rumor is
Speaker 261: true, then Charlie was possibly cremated to hide evidence of his murder, assuming the Mike theory is the truth. This aligns with other spousal
Speaker 247: cover-ups.
I do think
Speaker 247: it's interesting that when she was asked, where is his body? She was like,
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): I'm not going to
tell you.
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): Can I have one thing? No,
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): you may not. You may tell us where he is.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): That's ludicrous. You need to look into the book. Lance Twitch was holding The Way of Kings,
Speaker 12: Words of Radiance, Oathbringer by Brandon Sanderson.
One of
Speaker 12: the key characters is an assassin.
That's weird. That's
Speaker 32: weird.
Speaker 258: I saw
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): the text about an email with Lance Twig's photo, potentially. I'll look at that. Who are the individuals
in the
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): car with Charlie? How many did the car seat?
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): There were five people in the car with Charlie. Any other reason a person would be hanging
out of a
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): car on a highway besides fearing for their life and trying to get help
Speaker 78: makes my blood boil.
Well, the
Speaker 78: argument was that they couldn't get him in the car.
The more I
Speaker 78: think about it,
the more
Speaker 78: ludicrous that argument becomes.
And I think that story
Speaker 78: that Frank
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): Turk was planting might have been, or Brian Harpo, I can't remember which one, planted the story of Charlie
Speaker 66: hanging out and someone hanging
out, someone
Speaker 66: else holding. I think it was all BS.
Speaker 66: because if he's truly dead, just fold him
Speaker 101: up.
Fold him up. Put him in. He's not
Speaker 62: fighting you.
Move his legs and close
Speaker 62: the door. I mean, even if you just like put, I mean, just move his legs and close the door.
Rather than
Speaker 62: having someone risk falling out at highway speed on the way to the hospital. Come on.
I really
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): believe that
was planted in case
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): a photo came up of this incident.
Or in
Speaker 18: case people realize, like we did tonight, there's audio recording of this incident. I
love
Speaker 78: your show. I saw this photo of Lance Twiggs from the Daily Mail when it first came out, but I don't understand how the Daily Mail confirmed
Speaker 21: this. Without the furry getup, he looks indistinguishable to me. Well, they were obviously tipped off where he was. I
mean, it looks
Speaker 21: like him. To me, it looks like him.
It looks like him
Speaker 12: to me. I
Speaker 78: can't.
Speak
Speaker 78: for everyone. I'm giving up all television and YouTube podcasts during Lent. It will be hard, and I miss you all. Jesus did so much more for us,
Speaker 247: and my eyes didn't go squiggly when I typed this. Blessings during the holy season. I think Mrs. Coleman and I may be giving up coffee, switching
to tea. We tried it today to
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): make sure we could get through.
This was the cup
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): I used.
It was
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): delicious.
It
Speaker 323: wasn't an Earl Grey tea, but it kind of tasted like an Earl Grey tea. I
can still
Speaker 324: smell it in here.
Yes, the B for real
Speaker 21: barren podcast. Blessings to you during the holiday
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): season. We'll be here when you get back. We're not going anywhere. We're not going anywhere.
Weird
Speaker 66: how we're always been told he was trans boyfriend, yet he still looks like a guy. Wouldn't this have been the perfect time to transform fully to a
Speaker 78: woman? That's weird, isn't it?
I
Speaker 78: told you I never believed it. I
told you
Speaker 78: I never believed he was trans and I never believed he was a furry.
Because I've never
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): seen him in a furry. I saw him in a hoodie
that had a
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): face on it.
Doesn't mean
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): you're trans. And I've never seen any evidence that he was
Speaker 63: transitioning. Just watch the show. We're ahead of everything over here. We take care of everything before it shows up.
You
Speaker 63: don't have to worry about it. We'll keep you informed. I've been watching
Speaker 78: you grow in your podcast while investigating CK assassination. There was a guy seen walking at the end of a video after things looking like Lance Twiggs. Was this determined? Not sure. Well, somebody said they emailed me a video that might be him, so I'll check that.
I
Speaker 38: will check it in the opening. You forgot about detective van after bringing OJ's sample blood to the crime scene during the investigation,
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): basically tainting all blood evidence. I can
only put so many things in
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): the opening. It was already clocking in at like 1700 words. I didn't forget. I just, I
try to keep them
Speaker 261: under like, I do word counts as I go and I just, and I trim and I add, I try to keep them under
Speaker 24: 1500 words if I can.
Speaker 24: 1500 words usually clocked in about 11 or 12 minutes but you know I did one that was close
Speaker 325: to 3000 words it was like a 25-minute opening I try not to do that to you guys but it was good it was so good
I didn't I
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): didn't want to cut anything I kept looking thinking no it's all staying you guys just got
to get
Speaker 326: over it
sorry
Speaker 3: has anyone pinged
cell phones that
Speaker 130: answers that question love your show and the hard work you're doing
go
Speaker 130: Max
Speaker 327: Barrett. Jesus loves you and your family, and so do I.
Speaker 3: Well, I love you too. Christ is king. Thank you. Christ is king indeed. Working
on it,
Speaker 3: working on it. Shortly
Speaker 173: after Nick Simp murder, ex-hub
and I went
Speaker 38: out to eat. Fred Goldman, Ron's dad, came over to the table. You're
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): our son's twin. We can't stay. Yep, he was.
Speaker 328: Oh, that breaks my heart.
Fred
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): Goldman is how you grieve in public, Eric. If you're looking to take acting classes, I know you fashion yourself as an actress. Go
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): watch, and
I know
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): she's probably too young for this because she's 36, so she'd have been born in 88. Yeah, she'd have been eight years old when the OJ thing happened. He doesn't remember watching Ron Goldman grieve on TV. I
Speaker 329: do.
That's how you
Speaker 329: grieve, Eric.
Go watch
Speaker 329: Ron Goldman.
oh
Speaker 1: please ah but we can't miss the mistake because we are the only high we are only high q and we don't ride small horses right here
Speaker 330: no we don't
mess
Speaker 18: with tiny horses midget horses or small
horses only
Speaker 18: the biggest horses
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): will do for this program ma'am only the biggest um
Speaker 21: Erica could have
Speaker 331: been in Provo then was dropped off at Signature. Yes, she could have been. First, safety chat. You are blessed with wit, wisdom, and winsome. You
trying to win me
Speaker 331: over with flattery because it's working.
Speaker 206: This keeps this for... Thanks for keeping it PG. Doing my best. I do try to keep it clean. Miss the challenger, La Quinta, under the tree. Quite confident. I
Speaker 251: don't think so. I've looked at that a thousand times.
Speaker 251: Details to email from Edward. Lyman
Speaker 38: owns prop dirt with lot van with truck adjacent to ROTC.
I looked that
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): up. I didn't see Phil Lyman. I saw someone else. I
apologize if I
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): got that wrong.
But I don't
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): think I missed one in the
parking
Speaker 334: lot.
Speaker 334: Thank you for seeking the truth. My family and I have been interested in converting to Catholicism. Baron, you've had an impact in that. Keep being the beautiful, bright light and soul in
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): this world. Much love to you. Mods are the best on YouTube. God bless you all. God bless you as well. Thank you, Brandy. Good luck with your search for truth. I hope you come to a conclusion that benefits you for the rest of your life.
Speaker 38: Whatever that is. And I...
We do
Speaker 38: have
Speaker 24: great mods. I mean, they're able to keep things under control. It got rowdy in there tonight. There were like 29,000 people in there at one time, and I was watching it spin around so fast I couldn't keep track of what was going, but they looked
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): like they were keeping it clean. Thank you for that generous donation as well. EK cannot be human. Anyone in her
skin
Speaker 58: would have a nervous breakdown by now.
I think she's
Speaker 58: human.
you
Speaker 335: should write a book of baronisms. That's not me pulling a baron. That's being me. That's me being me.
Speaker 336: That's
Speaker 337: good. I like that. I didn't see. I didn't even realize I said that. Oh
Speaker 339: gosh. Yeah. See, I just say stuff. I didn't, I did not even know I said that, but
I guess I
Speaker 24: did. I'm taking your word for it. I remember saying something about that, not me pulling a baron, but that's great. Um...
Speaker 24: First ever super chat? Is
it
Speaker 17: possible the security guards monitoring the cameras for UVU saw everything and called the police? That's why they had that description two minutes after the Big Bang? I
suppose it's
Speaker 340: possible. I
did a FOIA request. Scratch
Speaker 342: that.
I
Speaker 342: don't think I did it. I think Brandy or Billy did it, one or the other.
In fact, I know I
Speaker 343: didn't do
it. I
Speaker 343: remember now getting it back. So no, Brandy or Billy, one of
Speaker 24: them did a FOIA request.
And I asked
Speaker 24: them, can you ask for the footage from the, I think it was them. Can you ask for the
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): footage from the walkway, the pedestrian walkway that goes over the interstate next to the campus?
And we were told
Speaker 274: they don't record. It's only live audio.
I
Speaker 344: mean, only live video.
I wonder
Speaker 344: if a lot of their cameras on campus
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): are that way.
Hi, Barron, from good
Speaker 38: old Dothan, Alabama. Would you kindly tell me how you got
your X
Speaker 38: account back? I'd love to get mine back, too.
Thank you
Speaker 38: for your work, Crisis King. I lost it
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): in early 2021. Got it
back in late
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): 2025. I begged. I
mean, 100
Speaker 24: emails,
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): maybe.
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): Finally get to
Speaker 24: the right person, I guess, and they're like, eh.
I mean, I do pay them every
Speaker 24: month. You've got to buy a membership, right?
Now, keep
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): in mind,
I did
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): not get my followers back,
but whatever. It
Speaker 37: was worth it.
It was worth
Speaker 37: it. Dispatcher gives into broadcast 1511
Speaker 315: when Bolo went out for Zachariah.
I
Speaker 315: wonder what that meant.
Couldn't Erica
Speaker 315: be on the
Speaker 292: N-40 JD flight? That would explain why the timeline matches the police chatter, and she would have gotten there before Andrew. Let
me
Speaker 345: pull that up and look.
Could have
Speaker 346: been?
could
Speaker 347: have
Speaker 348: been, but she would have still had to wait around for an hour or two until the next flight showed up. That could have been Andrew. So
she
Speaker 313 (lower-pitched voice): still wouldn't have been there in theory. According to her story where she said she landed and went immediately to the hospital, she still wouldn't have been there when Andrew showed up. So either way, there's still a discrepancy.
Speaker 348: Wow. Something has woken me up two times since going to bed at 10 p.m. in UK. Convinced now
Speaker 348: It's
Speaker 3: so I'm able to leave this super chat on 2501. Oh, on January 25, because you're overseas and you
Speaker 251: guys do everything backwards. I emailed you a super detailed timeline of the flights on 10-9, on 9-10.
Love
Speaker 3: you. Thank you for doing that. I'll have to go back and look. January 25th? A while ago.
Why so sure the
Speaker 3: Delta Zulu flight
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): could have gone to...
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Signature, not Duncan.
Speaker 349: Because the ADS-B ends its signature. Now, I guess they could
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): have turned the transponder off and kept going on to Duncan.
I mean, maybe. But that's
Speaker 352: why.
I hope you're
Speaker 93: going to explain what Erica did from 10.06 to 3.12 and how nobody at Duncan could have seen her. I think she was on the plane.
I think she was on the
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): plane. The plane that had the stairs down, the Egyptian plane. That's my guess. Look, I could be wrong.
But I'm
Speaker 192: trying, look, thank
you for that. I'm trying to
Speaker 192: synthesize
Speaker 19: all available facts.
I'm
Speaker 19: trying to work it all together and think, why would Andrew have said he fell into Erica's
Speaker 37: arms? Why would Erica not know if Andrew's wife was on the flight?
These seem like pretty
Speaker 353: simple things to resolve.
And the
Speaker 353: answer is that
they're
Speaker 19: lying. That
she was
Speaker 19: there early, that Andrew flew in before we thought he flew in.
And
Speaker 19: that she was not able to leave to go to the hospital until Andrew flew in because Andrew, I mean, she wasn't supposed to be there. And
so when
Speaker 19: Andrew flew in on that flight, they
saw each other, fell into each
Speaker 19: other's arms. I mean, I'm just trying to make it in my head, synthesize everything they said.
That's all.
Speaker 354: uh why would eric yeah so that's it that's why no
i i think i explained this there were multiple reasons
Speaker 355: i hope you heard my answer early i don't want to go back through but i think i think i
gave
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): you four or five reasons why i think she would want to be there situation room not have to explain to anyone in arizona why
she was
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): grieving weirdly
uh because
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): she was giddy i mean it looked like it
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): anyway
i mean do i have
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): to show you the picture of her laughing five days later on the zoom call about the thumbs
up
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): which, how many Zoom calls you been on? A thousand? You
ever laughed
Speaker 356: about, you ever heard anyone
laugh about
Speaker 356: the thumbs up?
The
Speaker 357: thumbs are going off.
It's
Speaker 211: weird. It's weird. Yes,
the
Speaker 3: guy driving hospital to hospital was driving a white Toyota Corolla. I think it was a black Toyota Corolla. Did they say white? I thought it was black. Either way,
I think
Speaker 3: that's the guy.
After these last
Speaker 39: few episodes, it's hella important to say Baron isn't suicidal.
or is
Speaker 39: that too serious and crazy for them?
Don't
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): fight with my mods. Don't
fight with the
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): mods. We
don't need to go
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): that way, but
I'm not
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): just to clarify. I found
a video
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): of Lance twigs on campus. Everybody's saying this, please send it to me. Should I just look it up? Is it on X or something? I mean, is this easy to find? Cause
I've got like three
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): comments now that have said they found it.
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): uh let's see wait
Speaker 358: a minute what was that that's weird um travis your your x-fees driven
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): me out lately if you're watching um lance twigs on campus let's see
here i spelled
Speaker 359: campus wrong
photos of lance
Speaker 360: twigs on campus uh Thank you.
I don't see
Speaker 223: anything. Email it to me. Realbaronpodcast.gmail.com. If you email any other email, it just gets deleted before it's opened.
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Again, I get emails or texts from people saying, I'm trying to email you, it's bouncing back, and I go look and my other emails are full of video clips.
Speaker 247: Please don't email any other email address. Realbaronpodcast.gmail.com. But if you'll email that to me,
I'll be
Speaker 247: happy to
Speaker 38: take
a look
Speaker 38: at it.
The
Speaker 38: FBI doesn't want to be attached to it now that the
Speaker 206: people aren't letting go. They
think we
Speaker 206: will just forget they were part of this so they can blame it on local law enforcement. Just admit it was fed slop already, FBI. It was the fedest and sloppiest. Spell check, please. Details in, not to, email from 2.15, 1.04 a.m. Dodge under the tree before Panorama,
Speaker 334: Pam Laquinta to track between Dirt Field and ROTC. I'll
Speaker 220: look.
Speaker 220: Oh, you're saying it was before the La Quinta.
Dodge under
Speaker 220: tree. I'll
look
Speaker 153: because if you can solve this mystery for me, I will be as, I
Speaker 198: mean, I'll just be tickled pink.
This may mean
Speaker 198: I'm going longer than three hours again at night, and that's going to cause everybody in my emails to panic. I can't
Speaker 361: commit to more than three hours. Well, then don't.
I put
Speaker 362: chapters in there. You're
free to
Speaker 362: click around. You're free to, you
know.
Let me
Speaker 362: look. I'm close. I'm
Speaker 211: close. It's opening. We'll look together, shall we? We
will look
Speaker 211: together, ladies and gentlemen. You're
saying
Speaker 47: the dirt field
Speaker 363: between the ROTC building. That's
the ROTC
Speaker 363: building. That's the dirt field.
Dodge under tree before
Speaker 331: panorama pan La Quinta.
Speaker 331: Two-track between Dirt Field and ROTC.
I don't see one on the Dirt Field. Anybody see one on the Dirt Field? I don't see one. Still don't see
Speaker 365: one.
Was
Speaker 365: that what you're talking about? No, those aren't Dodgers.
Speaker 366: I'm not tracking you. I'm sorry. I would love for you to be
Speaker 367: right because that would just be an absolute solve. If I can put his car somewhere, my whole analysis of this case changes. I cannot find his car anywhere. Guys, I've
looked, no
Speaker 198: kidding, at every street and every driveway in this image. Every
street and
Speaker 198: every driveway.
Speaker 198: hours and hours and hours we'll just zoom in painstakingly looking at every car in every driveway up and down every one of these streets
at
Speaker 368 (lower-pitched voice): this pace looking for everything i can possibly find and then marking off on a map next to me every street that i've looked down there is no car anywhere that's not
one by the way
Speaker 293: four-door um
so i'm
Speaker 293: trying over here people i'm trying to make it work if you if you spot it let me know uh
legend well
Speaker 293: thank you 44 is that like a special number was that your high school football number or something were you number 44
i love your
Speaker 293: extensive work
well i
Speaker 369: love your
extensive comment
Speaker 38: brevity is the soul of wit
Speaker 38: I'm probably behind. If Tyler uses an iPhone, all Lance needs is Apple device access to iMessage linked
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): to Tyler's phone to fabricate the messages. Good point.
Didn't think
Speaker 211: about that.
Did not think
Speaker 211: about that. I started watching you and now my husband Bob watches with me
Speaker 130: every night. Hi, Bob. He's currently traveling. Oh, sorry. But watching you all the way. Hi, Bob. Please
say hi
Speaker 130: to him. Hi, Bob.
as a
Speaker 130: surprise.
Speaker 13: We've been married for 34 years. Crisis King. Crisis King indeed. Happy 34-year-iversary.
Speaker 370: Bob,
if that is your real
Speaker 370: name. I'm
so
Speaker 223: thankful for your dedication to this investigation. I'm so thankful for your dedication
to that
Speaker 223: comment. Thank you. You're welcome, I think.
Speaker 223: Uh, when they make the movie,
Speaker 371: the big bang, who will you pick to play your character? Great work. Incredible show. Wish you were the head of our DOJ.
Um, who
Speaker 371: would play my character?
I can't think of anybody. Think about it. You got to be
Speaker 372: dashingly handsome. I'm just kidding. Um, who would
play my character? Hopefully
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): someone younger.
Speaker 315: So they don't have
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): a gray beard.
it's someone
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): that has a little more red in the beard, better hair that doesn't do this on the sides. You know, make
me look awesome. Maybe someone
Speaker 251: that's not 46 years worth of wear on their face. Make me awesome. And I'll appreciate it.
I have a
Speaker 251: novice scent dog and she can alert on one drop of three cents, 500 feet away. So advanced scent.
Speaker 251: Scent dog can
Speaker 315: find a scent miles away. I don't buy it. Great job, Baron.
God is king. God
Speaker 315: is king indeed. Hey, I
Speaker 293: don't buy it either.
I don't think
Speaker 293: there was a gun there when the dogs looked.
The dogs are
Speaker 3: literally trained to find guns.
And let me tell you something. When I was
Speaker 3: in high school, I had a really good friend.
I mean, he's
Speaker 3: still alive. It's not like he passed.
But his
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): dad was tangentially related
to the
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): scented dog industry.
And I was
Speaker 38: at their office and they brought in one of these dogs and they had, you know, little samples inside of jars and they would bury it around the office. These dogs could find, you'd take the dog out, you'd
hide it
Speaker 315: and the dog come in, boom, right to it. I
don't believe
Speaker 315: for a second that, that trained canines
Speaker 284: missed a rifle that two bumbling morons walked
Speaker 373: over and like, oh, there it is. It's in a towel, right there.
Not buying
Speaker 373: it. Nope.
Speaker 371: not violent not a gun that just was fired no way no way hi baron uh hi from
Speaker 38: sc south carolina first time catching you live at the beginning of your show my husband and i myself my husband and myself it's my husband and i the object of the preposition is me the subject is i
you would
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): do something for yourself
you
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't yourself do so.
Speaker 43: Enjoy watching your show. You may not enjoy it anymore now that you've got an English lesson, but Ms. Priss, we're all better
off for
Speaker 43: it. We're all better off for it. Thank you for watching.
Speaker 18: Welcome to the live program. I hope it's everything you hope for and more. And I look forward to you joining many more live programs about the same time, most nights. Most nights. Thank you
for your
Speaker 18: generous contribution. Tell your husband you
I
Speaker 18: apologize for the English lesson. I meant nothing by it. Please don't hunt me down. I'm too old to fight.
I'm too old
Speaker 47: to fight. I'm sure you're worth fighting for, but I'm way too old for it. So don't thank you. Mr. Amazing and
Speaker 284: Mr. Twigs are acquainted. Are
you calling Mikey
Speaker 284: McCoy Mr. Amazing and you're saying he knows Lance Twigs?
Speaker 348: uh t r i guess is what you meant was set up as the patsy the pick of mr t in texas doesn't someone in tp usa live in texas a deep dive into mr twigs would be revealing so you've put forth a lot of facts
Speaker 211: there that i've not heard um
if you
Speaker 211: can support those if with evidence please email me
Speaker 348: realbaronpodcast at gmail.com i'll be happy to review what you've said
uh what are we
Speaker 348: the people going to do about
Speaker 374: what we know
I'll
Speaker 375: say this. I'll have a lot of difficulty voting in 2026 or 2028 unless the DOJ comes clean with
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): this case and the Einstein
files
Speaker 37: and everything else. I went back to the polls in 2024 for a specific thing.
Speaker 4: Transparency in government,
Speaker 29: honesty, honor, integrity. I did not come back to be BSed with a bunch of bull butter. I just
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): didn't.
And if
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): you, you have to earn my vote,
you have
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): to earn it every
Speaker 1: time. And
you're not going
Speaker 1: to convince me to go slavishly going to the polls. I'll cast an empty ballot. I want to keep my perfect record of voting in every election, but I'll just cast an empty ballot. I'm
so irritated with the
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): way this administration is unfolding. It's, it's become ridiculous. It's become ridiculous. Love your show. everyone should love and like
That
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): show, best opening ever. Oh, thank you. You must have learned something about the juice.
Sent video of exactly
Speaker 3: what made CK's shirt do what it did. If it's the Henshaw video, I've seen it, but I'll check it
Speaker 38: out. I'm
well aware
Speaker 38: of his work. My
dad was an
Speaker 38: engineer on the space shuttle. He said they couldn't have done the shuttles without the knowledge from the moon landing.
I'm not going
Speaker 251: to destroy your conversations with your dad. I'll
just say we
Speaker 251: politely disagree. We
politely
Speaker 3: disagree. Why
do you
Speaker 3: think nobody's talking about Cabot Phillips anymore? He seemed like an interesting character in the Fort Huachuca
Speaker 162: story. He provided an alibi. He gave a stern denial that he was there.
I
Speaker 376: don't know I don't know you're familiar
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): with Smith-Mund Act thanks God bless you maybe let me look it up Smith-Mund Act
Speaker 377: oh is this the let's
Speaker 378: see here January 1945 I don't know that I
am
The
Speaker 378: Smith-Munt Act
Speaker 198: developed to regulate broadcasting of
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): programs for foreign audiences produced under the guidance of the State Department. It prohibited the dissemination of materials produced by such programs as one of its provisions. The original version of the act was amended, which allowed for materials produced by the State Department to be made available within the United States. Oh,
so the
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): amendment was so that they could serve propaganda on us
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): here on the homeland. Yes,
yes, yes,
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): I've heard of it.
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, thank you. I appreciate you as well. Wow. Courtney, thank you.
Speaker 4: Barron, great opening statement. I still think OJ had something to do with it. I think it had to do with the cover-up. Lance Twiggs was also the one who found and destroyed the note. Convenient. Found.
Speaker 3: Destroyed.
Love the
Speaker 3: research and things you bring to light. Definitely high IQ. Go max bad cop. Yes, we're bad copping all over the place up here. I
need a
Speaker 3: bad cop hat, don't I?
That's what we
Speaker 379: need.
Speaker 355: That's the first hat.
Do
Speaker 355: you still think if burned, there was a smell?
I don't know. I don't know, because it would
Speaker 381: have been quick. It
would have been
Speaker 381: quick. He looked burned. His hands looked burned. His arms looked burned.
Have I seen my two animated
Speaker 377: videos on Fleet's channel? Oh, my heavens. I laughed so hard. I've seen one of them. Is
there a
Speaker 377: second one?
I
Speaker 211: don't know that I've seen the second one I saw one where I was just totally jacked more of that please more of that 80 Fleet has Colin looking so
Speaker 367: jacked I don't even know what to do with it I don't think I've seen the other one
I'll have to
Speaker 367: try to find it
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): yeah We'll
Speaker 87: see you next
Speaker 382: time.
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Colin looks so jacked. I don't want to look that big. I like the one
that I
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): had.
Speaker 87: Oh, no, I did see them both. I did see them both. The crash out with subtitles and the Erica Kirk loves Baron
Speaker 334: and that creeps him out. Yeah, I saw that one.
This is the
Speaker 382: one where I was jacked.
We'll watch
Speaker 383: it.
this
Speaker 179: made me laugh
if you've not
Speaker 179: seen it they do great works
Speaker 8: this is a
job like somebody's job is
Speaker 8: taking out the trash that
that's their
Speaker 28: job there they clean up the the restroom they clean up the break room they they sweep the floors they make sure it's all picked up
we're going to
Speaker 28: give you forty three thousand seven hundred and fifty dollars a year for your services as long as the parking lot looks good. There's no cigarette butts on
the ground.
You
Speaker 2: know, there's no there's no brown skid marks in the toilet bowls. There's no yellow drips around the rim. We'll
get your
Speaker 353: money. You're going to get paid every two weeks. OK.
If you go to that guy
Speaker 353: and you say, I love you, that guy should look back and say, you're nuts like you are out of your mind.
no i
Speaker 230: love you i want you to go home and journal about your experience here my experience cleaning the
toilets you know somebody
Speaker 230: blew up
Speaker 384 (higher-pitched voice): the the toilet on the second floor you
know what i
Speaker 384 (higher-pitched voice): had to do pick
the peanuts
Speaker 384 (higher-pitched voice): and corn pieces out of the rim was that you lady
you
Speaker 384 (higher-pitched voice): love me go clean the toilet i haven't gotten i haven't
Speaker 146 (higher-pitched voice): finished it yet i had to take a break halfway through take my elbow length rubber gloves off and get
Speaker 72: on a zoom call it's
a high iq
Speaker 72: outfit that
was great that was great uh
Speaker 13: yeah 80 80 fleet does great work um and it's very flattering everyone looks hotter in the 80
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): fleet videos than they are in real life
I
Speaker 33 (lower-pitched voice): mean, Erica Kirk was like an eight in that video. Your humble host was like
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): a 10. Just kidding. Not in real life. Not in real life. Yes, yes, yes. They do a good job. Can I find Lance's car? I've looked. I've looked. Don't
think I haven't
Speaker 373: spent time looking.
Speaker 375: I have looked and looked and looked and looked.
And I have not been able
Speaker 375: to locate it.
Speaker 385: Um...
I
Speaker 386: agree, Your Honor. Shout
Speaker 370: out to Tyler's defense team, probably watching your show right now, taking notes between Barron and
Speaker 387: Candace's podcast. If they don't know, no,
now they
Speaker 387: know. I hope so.
Welcome to the
Speaker 387: program,
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): guys. I hope so. I hope they
Speaker 43: have somebody assigned to watch podcasts all day.
Speaker 43: You imagine that you're the new lawyer and you show up with your briefcase. You're like, I'm ready to write briefs. They're like, whoa, hold on, cowboy. Sit down, open your
Speaker 388: laptop. You're
going to
Speaker 388: watch 13 hours a day of
Speaker 247: podcast and you can't bill it to anybody. You're just going to do it. Okay.
Poor sap spent 200 grand
Speaker 389: going to law school.
Okay.
Speaker 388: he probably graduated like
Speaker 37: third in his class got all the different ropes on his graduation suit
and his
Speaker 4: job is to watch podcasts sun up to sun down every day he's got to watch Jesse on fire he's got to watch Ian, he's got to watch
Colin
Speaker 390: he's got to watch Baron, he's got to watch Candace all the people that go by on one name only he's got to watch them all
Speaker 211: yes yes yes that's your job my man if you've got to go and pee don't let us stop you don't worry we will behave while you're away why can't i trust you that's the problem there's a zoo in here already uh
please take
Speaker 211: care and rest when needed
Speaker 290: your podcast is
Speaker 206: brilliant god blessed and crisis came well thank you the old throat needs more rest than anything i yell too much now i know why candace is so calm she's got to keep that voice smooth as
butter your
Speaker 206: humble host can't
Speaker 261: help himself
We
Speaker 261: also can't explain how they always had fireworks go off at night after Charlie spoke, and there were no fireworks set up for that night.
Speaker 391: Ooh. Ooh.
Is that true? I was
Speaker 293: unaware. I'm
a member now, and
Speaker 293: I never want to miss a cookie story.
Speaker 332: You never
have to
Speaker 293: now.
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): The
member side is
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): just full of cookie stories. That's all we're talking about, cookie stories.
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, Baron, the clip of the police saying the FBI don't said, don't interview clearly says Andrew.
I'll have to go back and look
Speaker 315: at that. Is that true? Is this true? Um, how
do you know the golf was
Speaker 394: only at signature? FBOs can handle
Speaker 21: multiple jets. Okay.
Just
Speaker 21: depends on their specific agreement, not conclusive
Speaker 18: IMO. Look, I'm just my opinion, my opinion, my opinion. My brain is befuddled
Speaker 293: by barren.
Barn burner
Speaker 293: tonight. Thank you. I'm shooketh. I'm shooketh. Now
I know why my cop
Speaker 57: friends won't talk about this. They were there. Ooh, were they? You need to really poke at them.
you want to talk you can
Speaker 375: go to dinner
and go
Speaker 375: get coffee get
them in
Speaker 375: a sauna you cannot you cannot tell lies in a sauna if you're
in a
Speaker 375: sauna the truth just comes
out this comes
Speaker 206: flowing out of your mouth they call it the
truth barrel a few weeks
Speaker 206: ago i watched my first membership video and you were standing
Speaker 284: up revealing your tats hey don't
be telling people
Speaker 284: this come on
What
Speaker 284: happens on the member side stays on the member side. We don't talk
Speaker 69: about this.
Everyone needs
Speaker 360: to join. Tons of fun. Blessings to Mrs. Coleman. We ladies have her back and continued protection
Speaker 206: for your family. Thank you for that last part. Hey, but keep my
Speaker 381: secrets over there on the member side. We
don't need the
Speaker 381: general jury learning all the secrets.
Now they know
Speaker 396: secrets.
Speaker 8: Hmm.
does
Speaker 8: the
Speaker 38: podcaster's research on this case do anything to this in court? Is it possible his defense does not have any of these hypo-hypotheses?
It
Speaker 388: could. Now,
his defense
Speaker 397: might not use any, but they'd be foolish not to. Because we are, in my opinion, offering a range of things they can research
Speaker 371: I'll see
Speaker 398: you
next
Speaker 261: time.
a
Speaker 371: range of things that I think they could get admissible. You know, if you want to put
up a
Speaker 371: whodunit defense, I
think we established that
Speaker 398: tonight. You're looking for a guy with long hair and tactical gear
and a
Speaker 398: mask.
Speaker 399: So,
Speaker 261: Hi, Barron, my wife and I, and even our high IQ Husky, Zelda, must be a very high IQ
Speaker 247: Husky. Love your show. You, Candace, and Ian are the Triforce of Wisdom. You think this Robinson trial could be theater? His
Speaker 38: defense team is suspicious. I've addressed that quite a bit. I don't know yet. I don't know yet. There are times I wonder if they're doing their job, and there are times that I feel like they are doing their job. So we'll see.
Speaker 38: Uh, Koreshi graduated from South Lake, Texas high school in 2017 in college. He studied abroad to Jordan, learning Arabic. He was assigned to the Netherlands on his LDS mission and served there before, uh, COVID-19 in 2020.
Well, you did a
Speaker 367: deep dive on that guy. I didn't know any of that.
I knew
Speaker 367: none of that.
Let's
Speaker 38: see. What else are you grumblers talking about over here? Baron, did you ever get with Stu Peters? I saw he was trying to talk to
you on
Speaker 38: X. No, I forgot. I forgot. I need to. Ian has been posting on X for anyone to test out the web.
Code
Speaker 47: word
Speaker 29: G-O-Y-I-M. All caps. Should
you want to
Speaker 3: play along at home?
It
Speaker 3: makes sense why they didn't have the normal ambulance at the scene, allowing them to take
Speaker 38: care of the final issues if needed on the way to the hospital.
That
Speaker 315: was my understanding.
That was my understanding. You
Speaker 315: grumblers are good tonight.
I don't
Speaker 315: give a dom. Great commenter, by the
way.
Speaker 38: LVT, the security cameras used by Carbine in Orem, Utah, since 2023. They broke up with Flock, used for cars traffic in July 2025,
Speaker 3: with no reason.
Speaker 3: Axon in Arizona bought in November, 2025 with weird CEO.
That's your opinion
Speaker 3: that he's weird. It's all good facts, but that's, you know, I don't want to call them weird. Carbine's AI triage grabs live video with zero eyes gun detector. AI rolled out of 200 plus Utah schools via $3 million contract. LVT Orem
Speaker 38: area HQ provides full service remote camera and data acquisition solutions.
Speaker 66: Dom's going deep on flock. Baron, have
Speaker 13: you and the missus tried mushroom coffee? No. Try the brand micro ingredients. I totally switched eight months ago and will never go back to the bean. I'm
willing to think
Speaker 13: about it. God bless you too, right? 76. God bless you too.
Coming in
Speaker 13: late. Sorry if you've already answered
Speaker 293: this. Can you get the dash cam footage through a FOIA request? You can try. I encourage you to.
I
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): encourage you. Baron doing squats. Big booty, Baron. Man love Thursdays. Man love Thursdays. Thank you. My fellow global war on terror vets will know. Oh,
you guys did man love
Speaker 400: on Thursdays in the global war of terror?
Like a lot? Like past first
Speaker 17: base? Yeah.
Speaker 17: Quick question about the Cabot Phillips, the Cabot. Were you able to
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): tell the difference enough with the candy to know if it would have been September 8th? No, it would have been a long time before that. Three months prior? Probably. I
know the magazines
Speaker 334: were a big clue. Crisis King? Crisis King, indeed. Super chat advice. Type in notes, copy and paste.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): That's great advice. I need to use that myself because
I always get
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): screwed up when I'm trying to give super chats to people,
Speaker 315: and I can do a lot of them.
But
Speaker 315: Barron, we watched Candace. Oh, you watched Candace, who led me to Ian, who led me to you. Oh, great. First time I saw your show was when you flipped out because a Rob McCoy video disappeared live. I
Speaker 401: don't think flipping out. I didn't flip out. I
might have flipped out a little. It was weird. It was weird. Someone
Speaker 371: should do a FOIA request with the FAA and get the air traffic control recordings for KPVU. That would
Speaker 58: likely tell us which planes went to which FBO.
I think
Speaker 58: that's available online for free, isn't
it? Daisy, if you're
Speaker 402: listening, is that available online for free?
I think it is. I think it
Speaker 403: is. I
don't know if you could upload satellite
Speaker 403: image to web. I
don't know that it would be able to
Speaker 404: interpret the pictures.
hmm you stated from
Speaker 31: mclintock's picks we
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): haven't seen um that he was very much not alive same reason you said jesse's theory doesn't work no
need for more he
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): looked pretty dead to me i
think he was unless
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): he's an
Speaker 405: excellent actor your 85 year old mama watched me for the first time last night a lot for a first watch i'm in it preparing i'm on it
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): Texas property manager, tell your mother that we're happy to have her. 85, that's a long
Speaker 406: life. Your elegant glass can be created by gluing a mason jar on top of a clear candlestick.
Secret is
Speaker 406: out.
Speaker 407: Yeah, but it won't
look
Speaker 406: like this.
Well, I guess you're saying it
Speaker 408: will look like
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): this.
Well, but
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): if you buy it, then someone else
has already
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): done the gluing.
And you
Speaker 409: can look fancy.
Normal episode tomorrow
Speaker 371: with
Speaker 206: members hang out afterwards. Looking forward to the climax of the Kirk investigation. I
could do
Speaker 206: that.
Speaker 38: The problem is as soon as I get done, there's some production that I have to do on YouTube. I have to trim the two-minute countdown out. I have to add chapters. I have to throw in a thing. So it
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): might be
like a
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): little, and I usually have to take a comfort
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): break.
like
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): I will tonight because I'm dying inside. So it
Speaker 24: would
definitely
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): have to be some time in between. It would definitely be some time in between.
What car is that? I just noticed a car I've
Speaker 410: never seen before. It's parked behind everything.
How did it get
Speaker 349: there? Weird. Never noticed that before.
Speaker 411: J.D. says his receptionist informed
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): him of C.K.'s murder. He never mentioned Mikey McCoy's call. J.D. said he went straight to DJT's office to tell the president who is lying.
Let
Speaker 412: me be fair to Mikey. He
might have called him
Speaker 412: after the receptionist and after he talked to the president. I don't know what the timeline was like, but apparently it was very quick.
It must
Speaker 412: have been super fast.
It must have been
Speaker 413: super fast.
Speaker 192: Oh, I have 2020, I have
Speaker 38: 2012 spring, 189 pages commencement email, realbaronpodcast at
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): gmail.com. I
don't know the best way
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): to email 189 pages unless you have it digitally on a link,
then just
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): send me the link. Put commencement
in
Speaker 3: all caps so I will see it. Commencement. That's amazing. I've been looking for this. I've been asking for it. I've been sending emails, making phone calls to the school.
No one
Speaker 3: will provide it for me. If you have it, that's absolutely amazing. I want to read it.
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): I want to look at it. There's something very specific I'm looking for. I cannot tell you what it is.
Now, I'm not going to tell
Speaker 206: you now, but there's something extremely specific I'm looking for. Extremely specific.
So
Speaker 247: please, by all means, we the people, please email that to me. Realbaronpodcast at gmail.com.
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, go back and listen, 4220, as
Speaker 251: per FBI, don't interview Andrew.
Who is Andrew? Let me see if I can
Speaker 414: find it.
Speaker 415: Timeline. Use me. This is the one we're using. 4220.
Speaker 416: don't interview Andrew
man
Speaker 417: I'm coughing tonight Andrew
oh Daisy even
Speaker 335: put in the notes Andrew's name was mentioned here
Speaker 418: thanks Daisy
Speaker 419: alright let's listen I want to listen to this
Speaker 420: 42.20, you say? Is that right? Is that the right timeline?
Let's
Speaker 219 (lower-pitched voice): see here. 145.
Back
Speaker 153: we go. Back we go.
I will share
Speaker 10: it. We will all listen together. We're going to learn here, ladies and gentlemen. This is a high IQ outfit. It takes a high IQ jury to hold
Speaker 388: your high IQ host accountable. Here we go.
Speaker 216: just 10 14 i'm still about 15 out but
uh
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): the one day unit that's going to be up there to interview andrew as per fbi and fbi we've been given clear direction not to interview he
did say andrew i
Speaker 1: missed that on the original that was at 5 16 p.m so
no matter
Speaker 13: which timeline we use
andrew would
Speaker 13: have been there
Speaker 223: Now, have we been told Andrew was interviewed by the FBI that night? Is that common knowledge? Because I don't recall here.
Thank you for
Speaker 397: that high IQ super chat. Hmm. I'm
a former lawyer turned a much happier
Speaker 421: stay-at-home
Speaker 206: mom. Been here since Ian's first shout-out. Been hooked ever since.
Love
Speaker 206: your writing. See you writing the definitive book on the Charlie Kirk assassination cover-up
Speaker 247: one day. That would be a great idea. We've got enough material. I
could start writing
Speaker 247: on that now.
I could start
Speaker 247: writing that now.
A screwdriver
Speaker 251: would have been over by the pony wall where he laid down to assemble the rifle, not the imprint with a shot. By the way, I don't think it's TR.
Okay, I'm willing
Speaker 132 (lower-pitched voice): to accept that.
I'm
Speaker 132 (lower-pitched voice): willing to accept that.
Speaker 261: This is my first,
Speaker 293: now second super chat. You're 44 today. Happy birthday, Emily. Keep going, Max. You were doing yeoman's work. I'm doing my
Speaker 19: best over here. I'm doing my best over here.
If anyone
Speaker 19: interested in real Bigfoot vid,
Speaker 206: help a sister out. And it's up to Bigfootology.
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): I wouldn't ask, but my gov
is...
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): Stealing my paycheck to fund pyrotechnics, satanic rays. What? Huh?
Speaker 422: I'm
very confused. I
Speaker 244: am so confused. I
don't even know what
Speaker 244: to do with myself. I
saw a big
Speaker 424 (lower-pitched voice): super chat come in on Rumble, but I can't find it.
Where
Speaker 425 (lower-pitched voice): is you? Where are you, big super chat? Where are you?
There it
Speaker 290: is. Daisy is killing it. Yes, Daisy is killing it. Daisy absolutely is killing it. Thank you.
She even
Speaker 290: puts stuff in there that I don't see.
Speaker 405: Frank Turk said it was Brian Harpole hanging out on the car in his video. The greatness of Charlie Kirk and I witnessed count of
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): his
life in
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): martyrdom. Timestamp 5033. Yeah, my thought is that
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): Frank Turek might have been, I
don't trust
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): anything
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): that man says.
Let me
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): just say that up front. I just don't.
I don't, I just don't believe it. Frank
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): Turek said they drove about four miles to the hospital on surface streets, cutting through intersections and not on a highway.
BH
Speaker 198: door open must be footage.
Yeah, I'll show
Speaker 198: you the street they took because I know the route they took.
and they said
Speaker 198: they
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): drove well in excess of the speed limit as well. So this is the route they took. I've got this satellite image still pulled up, so I'll show it.
Where
Speaker 426: is it? There we go. This
is the street
Speaker 426: they took right here. It's a long,
Speaker 198: straight street. So
they would have had to cut
Speaker 198: these intersections. But it's this street running right up the middle. It's got a blue square going through it right now. There it goes. But it's this street right here.
And
Speaker 198: he said
Speaker 24: they were just flying at
their own
Speaker 24: intersection. So I'm guessing highway speeds. And I consider highway speeds anything over 55. I'm not
saying they
Speaker 24: were doing 100. But I wouldn't
Speaker 223: want to be doing
55 on that
Speaker 380: street going through those intersections and stuff with
the door
Speaker 380: open. I just wouldn't.
That's just
Speaker 380: me.
And
Speaker 427: that's just me.
Oh, this is
Speaker 265: interesting. Zechariah Qureshi was backstage before the Big Bang. I emailed you the photo. I'd
like to see
Speaker 428: that. I'd
Speaker 428: that. If it was emailed recently, I'd really like to see it.
Brian
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): Harpole during his interview said...
he
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): was the one hanging out of the car. So now we have Frank saying it. We have Brian Harpool
saying it. Duly noted all. Charlie
Speaker 3: Kirk alive after electrocution, sedated long enough to get to the SUV and out of sight, insufficient dose. Charlie comes to the chaos. Poor, poor Charlie. That's an interesting theory.
One of these
Speaker 206: days, I'll fix this cough. Darren, are you familiar with the life and times of the journalist Michael Hastings? I am.
If
Speaker 206: so, would be curious to hear your take theories on the 2013 sudden passing from a car crash.
I think
Speaker 335: he was taken out. He
was working
Speaker 335: on a big story
Speaker 298: and then his car mysteriously zoomed away and crashed and burst into a fireball, I believe. Baron, love your show and all your hard work. You
just need
Speaker 298: to defend my boy, Ian. He
only said
Speaker 298: that he pulled a
Speaker 429: Baron because that's what your fans were saying in the chat. Came from a place of love. I wasn't upset with him. It was love. I know.
I
Speaker 429: know, I get it.
What we
Speaker 251: don't realize is that
any one of us
Speaker 251: could hire a Bond-level hacker to hit the dark web and find all of these people's records, texts, calls, and on and on. The answer is there.
Really? Well, that's
Speaker 430: terrifying.
Speaker 431: Johnny!
Speaker 102: Girl! Thanks for the barn burner!
Speaker 102: Thanks for the big super chat, Shawnee.
Speaker 432: Wow. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. My goodness.
Thank you, Shawnee. You just
Speaker 360: humble me. I mean,
just so
Speaker 360: humbled. So
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): difficult to find the analytics, but I believe the history of abuse on Nicole is OJ did the first reaction would be
to get gut
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): punched, choke, Nicole, but the killer didn't.
Speaker 331: Okay. All right. Oh, wow. Baron warning, glorious.
Speaker 3: Oh, kombucha
Speaker 261: contains alcohol. Less than one half of 1%.
I will have
Speaker 261: 35 years sober, God willing, February 23rd. I'm familiar with the kombucha,
but
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): it's less than one half of 1%. I think you'd have to drink like
20 of
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): them in a
row in
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): like one minute to
equal a
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): beer. That's not going
Speaker 433: to happen.
Speaker 433: Um, but thank you for the fair warning and congratulations on 34 years sober. That's amazing. Who ate the cookie?
We love
Speaker 211: you. And also, can someone please tell me why in the world there's not a single Fox News anchor contributor that's willing
to
Speaker 3: question the slop, even just one?
Well, I
Speaker 3: can tell you they've been ordered to stay away from it. I can assure you, I can almost assure of you.
Speaker 3: Early
Speaker 261: on, facial recognition done by Jesse of Tyler on campus stairs was not Tyler at all, but matched Lance to a T.
Thanks, B,
Speaker 261: going Max.
Then he must have had
Speaker 405: his hair under his hat because he's got long hair.
He got long
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): hair.
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): would you take your children and go into hiding to protect them? Sent
you a
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): super chat yesterday, possibly EK at UVU immediately after big bang, added link and timestamp.
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah. Okay. Can you email that to me? Realbaronpodcast at gmail.com. I'll be happy to look at it. I've seen every image that people have sent me over the many months about thinking they saw Erica and I don't believe any of them are Erica, but I'm willing
to look at it.
If
Speaker 247: you're asking me if Eric is being normal, no. I would do exactly what Jackie Kennedy did, and I would go into Heidi. That's what she did with her kids. I
became a
Speaker 247: member today. Baron Coleman is
Speaker 13: now a line item on my monthly budget. Christ is king.
Speaker 8: May all lies be revealed. The truth set. Free biblical justice serve. Glory to God. Happy to be in your budget, ma'am. Happy
to be
Speaker 3: there.
Thank
Speaker 3: you, by the way. Thank you.
Was there an
Speaker 424 (lower-pitched voice): autopsy done? We're told there was an autopsy done. Erica Kirk has insisted there's been an autopsy done. You
should
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): do a show on transgenderism. I felt really, I first really remember hearing about it from show Jazz and the first pregnant man that was like 25 years ago would be nice
to do a
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): deep dive.
I'm probably not going to
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): do that. I'll be honest with you.
Probably not going
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): to do that.
Speaker 38: Uh, recall E.K. said I was never on Egyptian planes in an interview and no one asked guilty conscience. I
thought that was weird
Speaker 38: as well. Uh,
where do you think TR's
Speaker 38: team will go with their defense? I
wonder if
Speaker 38: they watch this podcast. One could hope.
I mean, ideally
Speaker 58: they, they point out that he didn't do it. He wasn't there or, um, maybe
they'll refer to some of the
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): radio we talked about today where they were identifying someone else.
I don't
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): know. I really don't know.
Really
Speaker 373: don't know.
Speaker 247: Yo, B, your show is great, man. Babylon System is the vampire sucking the blood of the children day by day.
Funny how the three men
Speaker 38: dressed in black walking past the Lyman house with the ring camera we haven't seen. They only showed us the limping guy that they're claiming is Tyler.
Speaker 370: Yeah. I'd
love to
Speaker 370: see those three go by.
uh
Speaker 434: phil phil
if
Speaker 1: you're there phil baron coleman here phil you guys released i believe to tmz if i'm not mistaken
image of
Speaker 1: a limping man walking
Speaker 38: down the street that you claimed was tyler robinson and even must have really looked at the zoom footage closely because there was a little hint
of a
Speaker 38: guy running in the back that i honestly being honest wouldn't
have seen meanwhile i
Speaker 43: Within an hour or so of the event starting, three men, all dressed in black, walked directly in front of that same house. Can we have that footage, please? Bill, please.
Surely you
Speaker 290: still got it.
Speaker 290: still got it. What if Frank Turek opened the car door to brush black plastic pieces off the seat and then couldn't get it closed again?
Well, Frank was in
Speaker 371: the back, I believe.
The
Speaker 358: backpack, like the
cargo
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): area.
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): so I think the door would have had to been opened by Brian Harpole, who allegedly was on that side, but yeah, same thing.
Sorry, too
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): many
Speaker 38: abbreviations earlier. Challenger under the tree
at La
Speaker 38: Quinta. Very confident. I
don't think it
Speaker 38: is. I've looked over and over and over. Go
Speaker 261: panoramic, southwest side of building, please see Dodge Challenger, Lyman property, chicken coop. I'll
have to look at
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): your email
because I
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): still don't understand
that because now
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): you're
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): talking about the Lyman property and the chicken coop.
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): So I don't believe the La
Speaker 198: Quinta had a Dodge Challenger.
I think
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): I've ruled that out every which way I can possibly rule it out.
I'll look again since
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): you're mentioning it. Southwest side.
Let's look together. I
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): don't want
Speaker 334: to be accused of dismissing it out of hand. So this is the southwest side.
That's north up
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): there. This is south down here.
I
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): see no challenger anywhere on the southwest side. Oh,
there you
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): go. Is that a challenger?
All right, I need my sleuths out
Speaker 435: here.
Speaker 24: Is
that a challenger
Speaker 24: at the La Quinta? Good call. I'm glad you sent three super chats to clarify this because I sure missed it.
You only
Speaker 436: got that one angle, right?
Speaker 437: Lee, is that a challenger? I don't think the trunk's long enough. I
don't think
Speaker 438: that trunk's long enough, but man, that sure looks like one. No,
I don't think
Speaker 362: it is.
Speaker 362: maybe uh the challenger comes up on the back and the back window is more vertical
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): and it has a longer trunk i believe but it's hard with the artifacts of satellite technology that looks more like a nissan sentra to me or
something like
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): that something in that class of sedan but
i'm going to have experts take a look
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): at it thank you for finally getting my attention
sorry i'm so
Speaker 439: dense
Speaker 93: sorry first membership I purchased first super chat as well
do you
Speaker 93: think TR will make it out alive and found innocent yeah if he's found innocent I don't know if he's going to be found innocent though I mean there's a lot of crimes he could have been guilty of there are tons of us starting
up
Speaker 331: groups there's no voting our way out of this it's time to stand up and take to the streets it's time I'm not
that's your
Speaker 331: opinion
And if
Speaker 223: you do it, I'm not going to say you're right or wrong. I just, I
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): don't want to be, I
don't want to be
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): on the record starting a riot or anything. But
I'm not going to
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): vote for them if things don't change. Like they have to change. They have to change. We
have to get what we
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): voted for in 2024, which was not this. It
was not
Speaker 264 (lower-pitched voice): this.
could
Speaker 334: have been anything if they didn't open the towel could have been a rifle shaped object a stick and a towel goes in the car a
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): gun and towel comes out I think they were saying they were going to open it when other people showed up
that's what I
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): think was happening
for all you
Speaker 34 (lower-pitched voice): asking if I've looked for Lance's Infinity yes
Speaker 38: I've looked as well I don't see it either
Speaker 38: E.K. had to wait for E.K. to arrive because I think he had
Speaker 93: E.K.'s phone. Fabulous show, Baron. Well, that's kind of my thought. I
need a shirt
Speaker 93: that says anti-Cookite.
Speaker 326: Duly
Speaker 43: noted.
Speaker 440: Duly
Speaker 441: noted. I vote for Jeremy Renner playing you in the movie. Who's that?
Jeremy
Speaker 442: Renner. He
looks nothing
Speaker 442: like me.
He's
Speaker 442: a handsome man, but he looks nothing like me.
He must be
Speaker 370: hilarious. Maybe he has a great sense of humor and a dashing personality.
Speaker 260 (lower-pitched voice): Frank's footage going directly to command center on N560 Tango
Speaker 443: Whiskey. Frank's footage going direct. Oh.
Speaker 443: Oh, so you're suggesting Frank may have had.
That may have been
Speaker 367: what he was filming because he was holding his camera up weirdly at the end. Maybe, maybe. I
would think they'd have
Speaker 367: other cameras up there,
Speaker 354: right?
They said they were live
Speaker 354: streaming it to the ops.
Maybe that's the ops. Maybe that's
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): the
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): ops.
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, didn't you spot what may have been an infinity with a rounded bumper on an episode
or two
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): ago by the La Quinta hotel when you were looking for Tyler Robinson's charger? Did I?
I'm still at the La
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Quinta.
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): Um, I
don't see what you're
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): talking about. Rounded bumper. I
see the blue car
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): someone emailed me about. Um.
I
Speaker 316 (lower-pitched voice): don't see the rounded bumper. No,
Speaker 368 (lower-pitched voice): I can go back and look because I've got my transcripts downloaded. I can
go back and
Speaker 368 (lower-pitched voice): look and see. Yeah,
I wish, man, because that
Speaker 367: would blow the case wide open.
If
Speaker 367: we can put the Infinity there.
It looks like a
Speaker 426: Nissan.
Speaker 444: Yeah, I don't see it. But
we tried.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): We tried, ladies and gentlemen. We tried. Do we know which vehicle Mikey got into? We don't. We don't. What do you think about the movie Snake Eyes Parallels? It's creepy. It's
Speaker 206: creepy. I don't
think
Speaker 337: it has anything to do with it, but it's 100% creepy. No doubt about that.
Speaker 445: it's creepy.
Speaker 3: There's so many parallels. You know what else I noticed about this? Hey,
listen
Speaker 19: to this.
So you
Speaker 19: know where Stacey Sheridan worked? Hey, Jesse, are you listening? Do you know where Stacey
Speaker 1: Sheridan worked before TPUSA? The
Gary Sinise
Speaker 1: Foundation.
do
Speaker 19: you know who's in the movie Snake Eyes? Gary Sinise. Gary
Speaker 159: Sinise is in the movie Snake Eyes. That
was weird to
Speaker 446: me. Yet another parallel that I've not heard mentioned. Yeah,
so...
I haven't
Speaker 298: heard that. So correct me if I'm wrong. Wouldn't George
Speaker 38: Zen go to jail or be part
of the
Speaker 38: murder investigation because he knew Charlie Kirk was going to be shot and that he'd be a decoy? Wouldn't that be an accomplice of the murder? I think
he's
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): going to jail for
images of young people. I think he's going to jail
Speaker 188 (lower-pitched voice): for that.
But I
Speaker 424 (lower-pitched voice): don't know
that it
Speaker 424 (lower-pitched voice): matters. He's old. He's basically doing life in prison.
I've been
Speaker 425 (lower-pitched voice): following you and Candace closely since the very beginning. I'm in Utah, not far from UVU. If you ever want boots on the ground, let me know. Thank you for all you do to find the truth. Well, thank you. Thank
Speaker 448: you for that offer. I may take you up on that one.
Speaker 38: Baron, you've inspired me, so I'm Catholic curious, lifelong atheist. Would I be allowed to attend mass and participate in confession? Or is
that only
Speaker 38: for confirmed Catholics? So you can go to confession.
Speaker 3: Just tell the priest I'm not Catholic.
because
Speaker 3: there's a little something they'll do differently at the end, but everything else will be
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): the same. So you can go to confession, check with the priest first, let them know you're not
Speaker 38: Catholic before you start. But I don't know a single priest on the planet that would kick you out. Like they'll hear it, but there's a little something at the end that'll be slightly different.
And you
Speaker 397: could go to mass. You're
not supposed
Speaker 397: to take communion if you're not Catholic. So
Speaker 449: just stay in your pew or walk forward. You cross your arms, you get a blessing from the priest. Some parishes are cool with that.
Just see
Speaker 449: what other people are doing. You'll see
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): other people either going forward and getting blessing or staying in the pews and
sort of hang out with them. But
Speaker 94 (lower-pitched voice): yeah, welcome. We welcome everyone. We
even sing a song that
Speaker 394: I can't stand called All Are Welcome.
Hopefully
Speaker 39: the parish you attend doesn't play it.
No offense
Speaker 39: if you guys like that song.
Speaker 38: Didn't Candace share a video
of the
Speaker 38: neighbors talking about seeing the shooter before the event with a girl before
she was
Speaker 38: quickly shushed? Yes. Yes, she
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): did.
it
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): was it might have
even been after
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): the event the girl said something about I think the woman he was with helped him change
Speaker 89: clothes and they were like why would they have a shooter up on the roof when they can easily using remote operated
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): weapons like they do in the Middle East someone can sit remotely and aim it using a computer
Speaker 450: great question Thank you.
And
Speaker 450: we're asking great questions here.
Speaker 258: No, it's not Everclear, my glass. Kidding. 13-year coin last November
after
Speaker 297 (lower-pitched voice): Boiv 68 have not been a good path. Going back.
Speaker 258: Thanks. Yeah, you should go back to church. Everybody should go to church. No, it's not Everclear, my glass. It's this hum beverage here. Delicious, a blackberry beverage.
And
Speaker 301 (lower-pitched voice): I've got my anti-autism Fiji water that takes heavy metals out of your brain.
I
Speaker 451: feel myself
Speaker 375: healing as we
speak. People
Speaker 375: say I move too much. I'm like, well, maybe the Fiji water will heal
Speaker 2: me. No, I read an article that Fiji water has enough dissolved silicone
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): or something in it. And it pulls heavy metals out of your body and helps you flush them. And I was like, all right, we're buying Fiji water.
That's why you see that
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): fancy water sitting there. I'm trying to get smart.
Speaker 206: uh did dw
Speaker 298: say where in texas he was spotted wondering if i'll running run into him at my local walmart did they mention the city i
Speaker 452: think
i don't know
Speaker 302: that they did i
don't know
Speaker 247: that they did um
can't wait
Speaker 247: for your mod pg whitaker 2 to get in the convo and give a stake on all this mr whitaker uh the
real
Speaker 261: umogy see email 213 7 23 p.m Thank
you very
Speaker 38: much.
Speaker 38: 63 possible same white truck with toolbox, black bed liner, TS5051, excavator
Speaker 350 (lower-pitched voice): truck with van, timestamp 13456, chip and coop, timestamp, second excavator, timestamp, does Lyman own construction company using construction to move culprits, allegedly.
Let me take a
Speaker 425 (lower-pitched voice): picture of that because I'm not going to be able to go through all that right now, but I will later. I'll look at
all
Speaker 287: that.
because
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): I didn't notice all the excavators BH said in gruesome detail how he reached into the wound
Speaker 247: and stretched the wound to see if there was an exit wound lots of strange details in Sean Ryan interview must re-watch in my opinion maybe fatal blow why would you reach in the wound to see
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): if there's
an exit
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): wound just look on the back
or maybe like
Speaker 283 (lower-pitched voice): put your hand on the back
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): see if it fills up with blood oh I'm not going to show that one
someone
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): commented on my pink hoodie and I'm not
going to
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): show it. It's not G-rated. I think an autopsy is mandatory. Someone told me that there might be an option where they couldn't do one, but she claimed there was an autopsy. She said, I've seen the autopsy report.
So...
I feel
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): that
Speaker 3: if we don't vote, we are complicit in handing it to the darkest side. But we're also rewarding the side who's lied to our face, basically, and said we're going to do all these things and then didn't do it.
I mean, so I... I don't
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): know. A car under the tree doesn't appear to have challenger rims.
I don't
Speaker 292: think. Go, Max. Do, la, do, do, da, loo, da, do.
Speaker 156: are we doing the coach do I owe him three dollars for that
do I
Speaker 156: owe him
Speaker 405: three more dollars for that I haven't clapped yet coach don't send me an invoice Christ is
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): king I love some coach love his live shows they're fantastic I let him play in the background while I'm getting ready
your hair is
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): going to be as long as Lance's by the time you get it cut no ma'am
you don't
Speaker 68 (lower-pitched voice): want to see me
Speaker 10: that way
Speaker 10: Uh, please do a woman's shirt with hope, please. I really want that one. I will. I will. We're getting a shirt. This is whole, please. We're also going to be back here at all likelihood tomorrow. Um,
hopefully we
Speaker 37: can go a little earlier. Um, again, uh, there was a lot, a whole lot of research that
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): went into this program. Give a shout out to Daisy, wherever you see her. I know she's active in the discord chat.
Speaker 368 (lower-pitched voice): Um, and she's amazing. Just amazing.
Speaker 368 (lower-pitched voice): has made this show infinitely better
Speaker 198: since bringing her aboard. So if you run across Daisy, give her a huge shout-out and a thank you. She's amazing.
And, you
Speaker 198: know, tomorrow
is going to be a
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): banger. If
we go
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): tomorrow, it's going to be an absolute banger. If not, I'll see you Thursday. I mean, Wednesday.
But I think it'll be
Speaker 171 (lower-pitched voice): tomorrow. I think it'll be
Speaker 156: tomorrow.
Speaker 156: uh, like comment, subscribe, notify, share with friends, timestamp, tell everyone how great you are. Tell them about the community. Everybody's
Speaker 19: dying for community these days. I mean, we
Speaker 8: are communal beings. Humans are communal beings. We're dying for community. And, uh, to the extent you can help someone find that community, then they will
thank
Speaker 4: you. They will thank you. They'll say, they'll say, but
chat, but
Speaker 4: chatter, but chatter, but chatter, but chatter.
Speaker 206: And you can explain how you
fall in love with
Speaker 206: these people. Cause
I fall in
Speaker 206: love with all of you. So thank you so much for being here. I'll be back soon. I'll be back soon. One way or the other. In the meantime, don't
Speaker 100: forget Jesus
loves you. Have
Speaker 100: a good night. We'll check back.